,geo,text,name,location,hashtags,source,followers_count,friends_count,created_at,verification_status,entities,sentiment
0,, STOP SAYING THIS IS THE 2ND WAVE OF COVID. You can’t have a second wave if you never came down off the first one. None of…,kaybirth,,[],Twitter for iPhone,742,243,2020-07-12 17:39:13,False,"[('2ND', 'DATE'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.109, 'neu': 0.891, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4466}"
1,," 🚨BREAKING: #Florida reports a staggering 15,300 new #coronavirus cases, shattering the single-day record of any state—pr…",monetmontague,"New York, NY","['Florida', 'coronavirus']",Twitter for iPhone,534,252,2020-07-12 17:39:10,False,"[('Florida', 'GPE'), ('15,300', 'CARDINAL'), ('the single-day', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
2,, ‼️37-year-old #Ohio veteran—who posted a widely shared anti-#mask screed on Facebook—tested positive for #COVID19 on Jul…,lynnsations,,"['Ohio', 'mask', 'COVID19']",Twitter for iPad,110,298,2020-07-12 17:39:09,False,"[('Ohio', 'GPE'), ('Facebook', 'ORG'), ('Jul', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.684, 'pos': 0.316, 'compound': 0.7184}"
3,,  mask is 1 step. Want to try to muster more votes? #LetFauciLead to finally control this #coronavirus. To seek his expert guidance would be a positive for u. Wish you’d understand he is not in competition w u. His focus: humanitarian wellbeing.  #sundayvibes,AMouseRoars,,"['LetFauciLead', 'coronavirus', 'sundayvibes']",Twitter for iPhone,5,60,2020-07-12 17:39:09,False,"[('1', 'CARDINAL'), '', ('Wish', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.83, 'pos': 0.17, 'compound': 0.765}"
4,," ⚠️As students have returned to campus, officials have been warning about an alarming spike in #COVID19 cases related to…",ander_the_table,,['COVID19'],Twitter for iPhone,638,4444,2020-07-12 17:39:09,False,"[('️As', 'CARDINAL'), ('COVID19', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.187, 'neu': 0.813, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4404}"
5,,#Trump home state. #DeathSantis is his Governor #COVID19 #coronavirus #CoronavirusPandemic #Coronavirusflorida #COVIDIOTS #WearYourMaskFL ,gibby0816,"Florida, USA","['Trump', 'DeathSantis', 'COVID19', 'coronavirus', 'CoronavirusPandemic', 'Coronavirusflorida', 'COVIDIOTS', 'WearYourMaskFL']",Twitter for Android,359,177,2020-07-12 17:39:08,False,"['', ('Trump', 'ORG'), '', ('DeathSantis', 'ORG'), '', '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
6,, Coronavirus: Why everyone was wrong--The immune response to the virus is stronger than everyone thought,this_danish,"Yeah, right.",[],Twitter for Android,88,172,2020-07-12 17:39:08,False,"[('Coronavirus', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.73, 'pos': 0.27, 'compound': 0.5859}"
7,, Homemade pastry.Corona makes me bake sweets.#SundayMotivation #coronavirus ,saqibf,"Karachi, Pakistan","['SundayMotivation', 'coronavirus']",Twitter for Android,34363,34530,2020-07-12 17:39:08,False,"[('Homemade', 'PERSON'), ('Corona', 'PERSON'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
8,, #Chinagovernment#IrangovernmentNations have been paying for their governments for thousands of years!To quarantine th…,Artemiss1990,#persia,"['Chinagovernment', 'Irangovernment']",Twitter for Android,400,475,2020-07-12 17:39:08,False,"[('thousands', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
9,, How #coronavirus affects the entire body Wale up Canada #WearAMask ,wholecloth,,"['coronavirus', 'WearAMask']",Twitter for iPad,699,440,2020-07-12 17:39:07,False,"[('Wale up', 'ORG'), ('Canada', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
10,,"His 276th visit to a golf course in his 1,270 days as president–more than 1 in every 5 days  #TrumpGolfsAmericansDie #coronavirus #COVID #Covid_19",Icingdeathe,Ethereally here...,"['TrumpGolfsAmericansDie', 'coronavirus', 'COVID', 'Covid_19']",Twitter Web App,1066,2255,2020-07-12 17:39:07,False,"[('his 1,270 days', 'DATE'), ('more than 1', 'CARDINAL'), ('every 5 days', 'DATE'), '', ('COVID', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
11,," So it looks like the GOP's strategy to use the #coronavirus pandemic as a holocaust against POCs, old folks, disabled f…",alisonserene,"Fort Collins, Colorado",['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPhone,219,703,2020-07-12 17:39:06,False,"[('GOP', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.873, 'pos': 0.127, 'compound': 0.4144}"
12,," Florida has had a record-breaking week leading to the all-time surge in cases. The state reported 514 fatalities last week, averaging 73 deaths per day. Three weeks ago, the daily average was 30 deaths.#coronavirus #HerdImmunity",bigpaulfla,USA,"['coronavirus', 'HerdImmunity']",Twitter for iPhone,199,621,2020-07-12 17:39:06,False,"[('Florida', 'GPE'), ('week', 'DATE'), ('514', 'CARDINAL'), ('last week', 'DATE'), ('73', 'CARDINAL'), ('Three weeks ago', 'DATE'), ('30', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.106, 'neu': 0.894, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5994}"
13,," . is releasing 8,000 inmates due to #coronavirus fears! 🤬 I’m fed up with his “leadership.” I’m seriously cons…",KsPatriotMadre,love'ѕ тнe only нoυѕe вιg enυғ,['coronavirus'],Twitter for Android,3654,5001,2020-07-12 17:39:06,False,"[('8,000', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.242, 'neu': 0.758, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5848}"
14,," 'When I was asked to support IT for the , I didn’t hesitate.' Find out how  Chief Information…",Scott1984FP,"Bedford, Bedfordshire, Uk,",[],Twitter for Android,2737,5001,2020-07-12 17:39:05,False,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.838, 'pos': 0.162, 'compound': 0.4019}"
15,," More than 69,800 people have died of the novel #coronavirus in 342 cities checkered across all of Iran's 31 provinces, ac…",besoyepirozi,"Arhus, Denmark",['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPhone,1425,169,2020-07-12 17:39:05,False,"[('More than 69,800', 'CARDINAL'), ('342', 'CARDINAL'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('31', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.145, 'neu': 0.763, 'pos': 0.092, 'compound': -0.3182}"
16,,"The National Population Commission (NPC) has said the continued closure of schools across #Nigeria due to the #Coronavirus pandemic might lead to an increase in teen pregnancy, abortions, and early school dropouts. ",ioaliu,Nigeria,"['Nigeria', 'Coronavirus']",Mobile Web (M2),502,533,2020-07-12 17:39:05,False,"[('The National Population Commission', 'ORG'), ('NPC', 'ORG'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE'), '', ('Coronavirus', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.931, 'pos': 0.069, 'compound': 0.3182}"
17,," ⚠️COVID-19 🦠 🚨Gov. DeSantis says schools ready to reopen next month, Florida Education Association disagrees.#SD13 #D…",TrumpWatchNews,"Florida, USA",['SD13'],Twitter for iPhone,1152,2757,2020-07-12 17:39:04,False,"[('🦠 🚨Gov. DeSantis', 'PERSON'), ('next month', 'DATE'), ('Florida Education Association', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.848, 'pos': 0.152, 'compound': 0.3612}"
18,," Not once, did she offer an idea to keep my baby safe. This is real and is NOT political.  You re attacking mine personally. AN…",larryinstafford,Stafford,[],Twitter for iPhone,2152,617,2020-07-12 17:39:04,False,[],"{'neg': 0.104, 'neu': 0.796, 'pos': 0.1, 'compound': -0.0258}"
19,," I had a gazillion questions before catching the #VandeBharatMission flight back to London from Mumbai. So, I hope you f…",MoniishaMishra,"London, England",['VandeBharatMission'],Twitter for iPhone,1929,186,2020-07-12 17:39:04,False,"[('London', 'GPE'), ('Mumbai', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.834, 'pos': 0.166, 'compound': 0.4927}"
20,, NCRI Women’s Committee calls on UN High Commissioner for Human Rights &amp; UN Special Rapporteur on the situation of human righ…,mostafaz22,,[],Twitter for iPhone,137,86,2020-07-12 17:39:03,False,"[('NCRI Women’s Committee', 'ORG'), ('UN', 'ORG'), ('Human Rights &amp', 'ORG'), ('UN', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.881, 'pos': 0.119, 'compound': 0.4019}"
21,," hey, quit being silly, you silly. Get a school backup plan for an outbreak. You're running a flippedy-do country, act like you give a stool sample and care!#schoolsreopening #coronavirus",BeardedQuack,,"['schoolsreopening', 'coronavirus']",Twitter for Android,8,8,2020-07-12 17:39:02,False,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.822, 'pos': 0.178, 'compound': 0.4574}"
22,, Follow .  Share the stories of so many lost to #COVID19.  Remind everyone that they are not just numbers. The…,tibbieman1,Phoenix,['COVID19'],Twitter Web App,294,1134,2020-07-12 17:39:02,False,[],"{'neg': 0.118, 'neu': 0.781, 'pos': 0.101, 'compound': -0.0972}"
23,," When it's time to wake up,even if you pretend to be asleep,the universe will wake you up by force.#Sufism_Awakening…",Artemiss1990,#persia,['Sufism_Awakening'],Twitter for Android,400,475,2020-07-12 17:39:02,False,[],"{'neg': 0.072, 'neu': 0.928, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.1027}"
24,," So it looks like the GOP's strategy to use the #coronavirus pandemic as a holocaust against POCs, old folks, disabled f…",IngridWonders,Canada,['coronavirus'],Twitter Web App,382,403,2020-07-12 17:39:02,False,"[('GOP', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.873, 'pos': 0.127, 'compound': 0.4144}"
25,, Russia first nation to successfully complete human trials of #coronavirus #COVID19 vaccine,shubhayush,"खेरली, Rajasthan","['coronavirus', 'COVID19']",Twitter for Android,340,212,2020-07-12 17:39:01,False,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), '', '', ('COVID19', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.775, 'pos': 0.225, 'compound': 0.4939}"
26,,  Crowds rush to escape #Coronavirus Droplet Cloud ,ten24get,New York City and points West,['Coronavirus'],Twitter Web App,5471,4351,2020-07-12 17:39:00,False,"[('Coronavirus Droplet', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.779, 'pos': 0.221, 'compound': 0.1779}"
27,, A regional testing centre has opened in Liverpool and will be accessible for Cheshire &amp; Merseyside residents experienci…,johnheritage123,"Warrington, Cheshire ",[],Twitter for Android,2237,4996,2020-07-12 17:39:00,False,"[('Liverpool', 'GPE'), ('Cheshire &amp', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
28,, #China is suspending imports of #meat and meat products from 23 companies and stepping-up inspection of imported foods…,Lancrunistuning,,"['China', 'meat']",Twitter for Android,435,1288,2020-07-12 17:38:59,False,"['', ('China', 'GPE'), ('23', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
29,," . is releasing 8,000 inmates due to #coronavirus fears! 🤬 I’m fed up with his “leadership.” I’m seriously cons…",emrellim,,['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPhone,771,821,2020-07-12 17:38:58,False,"[('8,000', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.242, 'neu': 0.758, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5848}"
30,,   The #COVID__19 scam must continue until Nov. 2020 as #AOC stated in her DELETED tweet... The #co…,BigTebowski13,,"['COVID__19', 'AOC']",Twitter for iPhone,0,87,2020-07-12 17:38:58,False,"[('Nov. 2020', 'DATE'), ('AOC', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.188, 'neu': 0.812, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5719}"
31,, Coronavirus: Why everyone was wrong--The immune response to the virus is stronger than everyone thought,LeWarriorSilenc,Everywhere,[],Twitter Web App,335,1358,2020-07-12 17:38:58,False,"[('Coronavirus', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.73, 'pos': 0.27, 'compound': 0.5859}"
32,," One thing #coronavirus has shown us, our lives are as pawns in the hands of rich legislators. Frontline workers, medical perso…",craigdadoly,"Austin, TX",['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPhone,233,638,2020-07-12 17:38:57,False,"[('One', 'CARDINAL'), '', ('Frontline', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.847, 'pos': 0.153, 'compound': 0.5574}"
33,, oh hai! I'm here with a friendly reminder that  has no plans to regularly test any of their employees #disneyworl…,PrincessxMisery,Pleasure Island,[],Twitter Web App,4554,189,2020-07-12 17:38:57,False,[''],"{'neg': 0.097, 'neu': 0.749, 'pos': 0.154, 'compound': 0.3164}"
34,, Coronavirus: Why everyone was wrong--The immune response to the virus is stronger than everyone thought,galvan5725,USA,[],Twitter Web App,367,388,2020-07-12 17:38:56,False,"[('Coronavirus', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.73, 'pos': 0.27, 'compound': 0.5859}"
35,," Epoch Times interview with Restart Leader:Iran's regime is killing Iranians!60,000 people have been contracted and mor…",Artemiss1990,#persia,[],Twitter for Android,400,475,2020-07-12 17:38:56,False,"[('Epoch Times', 'ORG'), ('Restart', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.238, 'neu': 0.762, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.69}"
36,,   Kneeling will magically end racism apparently; surely it wouldn't be better to solve the reason blacks…,PaulS1717,United States,[],Twitter for Android,182,513,2020-07-12 17:38:55,False,"[('Kneeling', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.28, 'neu': 0.517, 'pos': 0.203, 'compound': -0.4226}"
37,," . is releasing 8,000 inmates due to #coronavirus fears! 🤬 I’m fed up with his “leadership.” I’m seriously cons…",JuliusPetro4,"Ohio, USA",['coronavirus'],Twitter for Android,2058,2313,2020-07-12 17:38:55,False,"[('8,000', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.242, 'neu': 0.758, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5848}"
38,," TAKE A DEEP BREATHE«Remember to breathe. It is after all, the secret of life».(Gregory Maguire)  #medart #medicalart…",IAmMentzelTrash,,"['medart', 'medicalart']",Twitter for Android,733,1193,2020-07-12 17:38:55,False,"[('Maguire', 'GPE'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
39,, Democrats reviewing their platform #Trump2020LandslideVictory #KAG2020 #Tcot #Ccot#COVID19 #coronavirus #WalkAway #Saturday…,woonka,USA,"['Trump2020LandslideVictory', 'KAG2020', 'Tcot', 'Ccot', 'COVID19', 'coronavirus', 'WalkAway']",Twitter for iPad,596,912,2020-07-12 17:38:55,False,"[('Democrats', 'NORP'), ('Ccot#COVID19', 'ORG'), '', ('Saturday', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
40,," ⚠️Health officials in #Australia warn that child-to-child transmission of #coronavirus is ""more apparent"" than first tho…",LeslieMPozsonyi,"Melbourne, FL","['Australia', 'coronavirus']",Twitter Web App,1214,2073,2020-07-12 17:38:54,False,"[('Australia', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.085, 'neu': 0.915, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.1027}"
41,," Tomorrow isn’t promised, Just let him fucc.#coronavirus",bcasonnn,"San Bernardino, CA",['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPhone,295,239,2020-07-12 17:38:52,False,"[('Tomorrow', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.706, 'pos': 0.294, 'compound': 0.3612}"
42,," Ms MerkelWe had given you the ultimatum not to co-operate with the terrorist regime of Iran, otherwise, ISIS or smthing…",Artemiss1990,#persia,[],Twitter for Android,400,475,2020-07-12 17:38:51,False,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.198, 'neu': 0.802, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6908}"
43,," . is releasing 8,000 inmates due to #coronavirus fears! 🤬 I’m fed up with his “leadership.” I’m seriously cons…",bullseye7676,,['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPhone,40,207,2020-07-12 17:38:49,False,"[('8,000', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.242, 'neu': 0.758, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5848}"
44,," One brave woman sacrificing everything--home, family, career--will inspire others. There will now be many Chinese telling…",jbtalkingheads,,[],Twitter for iPhone,699,270,2020-07-12 17:38:49,False,"[('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('Chinese', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.664, 'pos': 0.336, 'compound': 0.7964}"
45,,Not all viral fevers are induced by coronavirus #Coronavirus #Infectiousdiseases #Viralfevers #Hyderabad ,TheHansIndiaWeb,Hyderabad,"['Coronavirus', 'Infectiousdiseases', 'Viralfevers', 'Hyderabad']",Hocalwire Social Share,5618,1633,2020-07-12 17:38:47,False,"['', '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
46,,#Masks will make you sick and or dead.There is a warning label on REAL mask.Promoting poisoning colds viral infections emphysema pneumonia hyperventilation causing nasal infection and death. #science Its not rocket science. Everyone has been exposed to #coronavirus already WTH ,CrazyKensTweet,"Phoenix, AZ","['Masks', 'science', 'coronavirus']",Twitter for Android,4,50,2020-07-12 17:38:47,False,"[('REAL', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.363, 'neu': 0.637, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.9574}"
47,, #digital…,digitalworking,"South East, England",['digital'],Twitter for iPhone,3018,2536,2020-07-12 17:38:46,False,"['', ('digital', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
48,,  I would risk my life to save that of any one of my students. I will not risk it or that of anyone close to me just so Trump can claim the #coronavirus  is being defeated.,FadingTeacher,"Virginia, USA",['coronavirus'],Twitter for Android,7285,7689,2020-07-12 17:38:46,False,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.18, 'neu': 0.741, 'pos': 0.079, 'compound': -0.4767}"
49,," So it looks like the GOP's strategy to use the #coronavirus pandemic as a holocaust against POCs, old folks, disabled f…",JohnWilkinspsyc,"Hoylake, England",['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPhone,605,600,2020-07-12 17:38:44,False,"[('GOP', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.873, 'pos': 0.127, 'compound': 0.4144}"
50,," 🚨BREAKING: #Florida reports a staggering 15,300 new #coronavirus cases, shattering the single-day record of any state—pr…",wickedatMLT,"Ohio, USA","['Florida', 'coronavirus']",Twitter for Android,131,603,2020-07-12 17:38:43,False,"[('Florida', 'GPE'), ('15,300', 'CARDINAL'), ('the single-day', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
51,," BOOM!Top pathologist: 'NO ONE has died from the #coronavirus!' | PSI, Inc. ",AndyBird21,U.K,['coronavirus'],Tweetbot for iΟS,440,845,2020-07-12 17:38:42,False,"['', ('PSI, Inc.', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.442, 'neu': 0.558, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.7974}"
52,, #China is suspending imports of #meat and meat products from 23 companies and stepping-up inspection of imported foods…,Unbelieveable6,"Victoria, Australia","['China', 'meat']",Twitter for iPhone,52,354,2020-07-12 17:38:42,False,"['', ('China', 'GPE'), ('23', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
53,,"2020 shall be known henceforth as “The-Year-That-Must-Not-Be-Named,” lest we summon its wrath#corona #hewhomustnotbenamed #voldemort #coronavirus #covid #covid19 #murderhornets #fire #australia #australiafires #ClimateCrisis #ClimateChange #ClimateEmergency",joshoptical,"Winston-Salem, NC","['corona', 'hewhomustnotbenamed', 'voldemort', 'coronavirus', 'covid', 'covid19', 'murderhornets', 'fire', 'australia', 'australiafires', 'ClimateCrisis', 'ClimateChange', 'ClimateEmergency']",Twitter for iPhone,104,163,2020-07-12 17:38:41,False,"['', '', '', '', ('ClimateChange', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
54,, #Pune #PCMC Are Lockdowns effective in reducing #coronavirus cases...? ,bhurtya,"Pune, Maharashtra, India","['Pune', 'PCMC', 'coronavirus']",Bhurtya1,836,34,2020-07-12 17:38:40,False,"[('PCMC', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.721, 'pos': 0.279, 'compound': 0.4767}"
55,, We are taking all efforts that everyone gets the best possible treatment. A point to understand though is that #Remdesv…,deshri80,,[],Twitter for iPhone,24,113,2020-07-12 17:38:40,False,[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.811, 'pos': 0.189, 'compound': 0.6369}"
56,," Internal documents from  warned fully reopening K-12 schools &amp; universities would pose the ""highest risk"" for spread of the…",Missin_Florida,🖕FuckTrump,[],Twitter Web App,30245,30357,2020-07-12 17:38:40,False,"[('K-12', 'PRODUCT')]","{'neg': 0.198, 'neu': 0.802, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4939}"
57,, Russia first nation to successfully complete human trials of #coronavirus #COVID19 vaccine,jaggi_pawanism,ನಮ್ಮ ಬೆಂಗಳೂರು,"['coronavirus', 'COVID19']",Twitter for Android,1503,1321,2020-07-12 17:38:39,False,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), '', '', ('COVID19', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.775, 'pos': 0.225, 'compound': 0.4939}"
58,," 🚨BREAKING: #Florida reports a staggering 15,300 new #coronavirus cases, shattering the single-day record of any state—pr…",MsStockman,,"['Florida', 'coronavirus']",Twitter for Android,49,491,2020-07-12 17:38:39,False,"[('Florida', 'GPE'), ('15,300', 'CARDINAL'), ('the single-day', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
59,, More cities to come under lockdown as India's COVID-19 tally surges to nearly 8.5 lakh | via  #coronavirus #C…,javirnitin1,"Thane, India",['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPhone,190,244,2020-07-12 17:38:38,False,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('nearly 8.5', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
60,, There is a team from the  currently in #China for an analysis of the global #coronavirus response but we know noth…,DonHectorHogan,,"['China', 'coronavirus']",Twitter Web App,33,310,2020-07-12 17:38:37,False,"[('China', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
61,,"#coronavirus update in #Eswatini. New cases confirmed 40, new recovered 12, new deaths 2. Total cases in Eswatini confirmed 1351, recovered 668, deaths 20. +3.05% daily cases increase, 40 reported today UTC time.",CoronaSpread,,"['coronavirus', 'Eswatini']",CoronaLiveUpdates,256,2,2020-07-12 17:38:37,False,"['', '', ('Eswatini', 'GPE'), ('40', 'CARDINAL'), ('12', 'CARDINAL'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('Eswatini', 'GPE'), ('1351', 'DATE'), ('668', 'CARDINAL'), ('20', 'CARDINAL'), ('+3.05%', 'PERCENT'), ('daily', 'DATE'), ('40', 'DATE'), ('today', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.933, 'pos': 0.067, 'compound': 0.3182}"
62,,"TAKE A DEEP BREATHE«Remember to breathe. It is after all, the secret of life».(Gregory Maguire)  #medart #medicalart #medicineart #lungs #pulmones #anatomyart #anatomicalart #lungsurgery #Covid_19 #medicine #medical #coronavirus #pulmonology  #lungcancer #sciart #ConceptArt ",saraillamas,Spain / Italy,"['medart', 'medicalart', 'medicineart', 'lungs', 'pulmones', 'anatomyart', 'anatomicalart', 'lungsurgery', 'Covid_19', 'medicine', 'medical', 'coronavirus', 'pulmonology', 'lungcancer', 'sciart', 'ConceptArt']",Twitter for iPhone,4584,418,2020-07-12 17:38:36,False,"[('Maguire', 'GPE'), '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', '', ('ConceptArt', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
63,, FROM ME: I interviewed Utah families who had a loved one die of #coronavirus. They say government has let them down and w…,skytsearle,,['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPhone,193,1559,2020-07-12 17:38:35,False,"[('Utah', 'GPE'), '']","{'neg': 0.146, 'neu': 0.709, 'pos': 0.146, 'compound': 0.0}"
64,,"The sociopath in the Oval Office thinks this is a political issue. The #coronavirus doesn't know or care who you voted for. We need a full, total NATIONAL LOCKDOWN for 3-4 months, with a 100% mask mandate any time anyone needs to leave their house for essentials (food, medicine). ",A4Ny14,"Queens, NY",['coronavirus'],Twitter Web App,8625,9304,2020-07-12 17:38:34,False,"['', ('NATIONAL', 'ORG'), ('3-4 months', 'DATE'), ('100%', 'PERCENT')]","{'neg': 0.08, 'neu': 0.92, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4268}"
65,," . is releasing 8,000 inmates due to #coronavirus fears! 🤬 I’m fed up with his “leadership.” I’m seriously cons…",Selena_M_Canale,"Santa Rosa, CA",['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPhone,2086,2601,2020-07-12 17:38:33,False,"[('8,000', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.242, 'neu': 0.758, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5848}"
66,, .It's too late. 👉You're seven years behind us! Continue with your censorship! We will see each othe…,Artemiss1990,#persia,[],Twitter for Android,400,475,2020-07-12 17:38:32,False,"[('.It', 'PERSON'), ('seven years', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
67,,"#AmitabhBachchan #AnupamKher #Covid_19 One more stupid Modi hater.👇Keep it coming guys, we shall put you all on ""Wall of fame #coronavirus 2020"" when its all over.😜 ",saying_as_it_is,india,"['AmitabhBachchan', 'AnupamKher', 'Covid_19', 'coronavirus']",Twitter Web App,638,208,2020-07-12 17:38:30,False,"[('AmitabhBachchan', 'ORG'), ('AnupamKher', 'ORG'), ('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('Modi hater.', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.121, 'neu': 0.784, 'pos': 0.095, 'compound': -0.2006}"
68,," 🚨BREAKING: #Florida reports a staggering 15,300 new #coronavirus cases, shattering the single-day record of any state—pr…",Washerein17,"Colorado, US","['Florida', 'coronavirus']",Twitter for Android,1907,2477,2020-07-12 17:38:29,False,"[('Florida', 'GPE'), ('15,300', 'CARDINAL'), ('the single-day', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
69,," She’s complicit, sinister and  definitely on the “Trump Train,” next slide! #coronavirus #ScarfLady ",DemocracyDC,Rent-Free Your Head,"['coronavirus', 'ScarfLady']",Twitter for iPhone,5675,6245,2020-07-12 17:38:29,False,"[('the “Trump Train', 'PRODUCT'), '', ('ScarfLady', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.234, 'neu': 0.615, 'pos': 0.151, 'compound': -0.3595}"
70,, This is the highest single-day total for any US state since the start of the #coronavirus pandemic.,OGCLEVELAND,,['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPhone,286,1168,2020-07-12 17:38:29,False,"[('US', 'GPE'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
71,, 🚨BREAKING: Commissioner in #Florida who *voted against #masks* has tested positive for #COVID19 and is currently in the…,eemc2,,"['Florida', 'masks', 'COVID19']",Twitter for iPad,90,138,2020-07-12 17:38:29,False,"[('Florida', 'GPE'), '', '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.825, 'pos': 0.175, 'compound': 0.5574}"
72,, AP is at Top 4 in India in #Covid19 cases today Maharashtra  7827Tamilnadu 4244Karnataka 2627AP 1933Delhi 1573 Telang…,jalaneelu,"Vijayawada, India",['Covid19'],Twitter for Android,92,810,2020-07-12 17:38:28,False,"[('AP', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('Maharashtra', 'ORG'), ('4244Karnataka', 'CARDINAL'), ('1933Delhi 1573', 'DATE'), ('Telang', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.899, 'pos': 0.101, 'compound': 0.2023}"
73,, #Florida's No. 1!...in #coronavirus. ,JosephTrento,"Naples, Florida","['Florida', 'coronavirus']",Twitter Web App,214,328,2020-07-12 17:38:28,False,"[('Florida', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.454, 'neu': 0.546, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.3595}"
74,,CHeck out my new track #UNBANPUBGPAKISTAN #PTALiftBanOnPUBG #ShehnaazGill #sundayvibes #coronavirus #QuarantineLife #quotes,ValiB0i,"Karachi, Pakistan","['UNBANPUBGPAKISTAN', 'PTALiftBanOnPUBG', 'ShehnaazGill', 'sundayvibes', 'coronavirus', 'QuarantineLife', 'quotes']",Twitter for Android,5,228,2020-07-12 17:38:27,False,"['', '', '', '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
75,," . is releasing 8,000 inmates due to #coronavirus fears! 🤬 I’m fed up with his “leadership.” I’m seriously cons…",CarolOSullivan1,,['coronavirus'],Twitter Web App,145,220,2020-07-12 17:38:26,False,"[('8,000', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.242, 'neu': 0.758, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5848}"
76,," Okay, retailers, if I'm asked to wear a mask, I can either show this card or wear this mask. We must #FightBack agains…",jcross_john,"Kansas, USA",['FightBack'],Twitter for iPhone,27511,27180,2020-07-12 17:38:26,False,"['', ('FightBack', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.913, 'pos': 0.087, 'compound': 0.2263}"
77,, ‼️37-year-old #Ohio veteran—who posted a widely shared anti-#mask screed on Facebook—tested positive for #COVID19 on Jul…,tibbidoe,"➡️ 🇺🇸, 🌎","['Ohio', 'mask', 'COVID19']",Twitter for Android,2247,2456,2020-07-12 17:38:26,False,"[('Ohio', 'GPE'), ('Facebook', 'ORG'), ('Jul', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.684, 'pos': 0.316, 'compound': 0.7184}"
78,, 🚨BREAKING: Commissioner in #Florida who *voted against #masks* has tested positive for #COVID19 and is currently in the…,irishgirlinatl,,"['Florida', 'masks', 'COVID19']",Twitter for Android,3,82,2020-07-12 17:38:25,False,"[('Florida', 'GPE'), '', '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.825, 'pos': 0.175, 'compound': 0.5574}"
79,,  How ya feeling #LittleTimmy? Perhaps you should get tested for the so-called #coronahoax you #COVIDIOT 🤦🏼‍♀️ You should definitely self quarantine.🙅🏼‍♀️ #coronavirus is not funny. Stay safe at home and away from people you love.🧼😷 Don’t be a spreader. ,ansue67,"Tennessee, USA","['LittleTimmy', 'coronahoax', 'COVIDIOT', 'coronavirus']",Twitter for iPhone,587,928,2020-07-12 17:38:25,False,"['', ('LittleTimmy', 'ORG'), '', '', ('♀', 'ORG'), ('😷', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.112, 'neu': 0.79, 'pos': 0.098, 'compound': -0.1561}"
80,, Germany and UK have similar population densities. Germany has a slightly higher population.#Coronavirus deaths in Germ…,fozhoath,,['Coronavirus'],Twitter for iPhone,43,69,2020-07-12 17:38:25,False,"[('Germany', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Germany', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
81,," ""On Friday, the Ohio Department of Health reported 62,856 total #coronavirus cases, 8,701 hospitalizations, and 3,032 dea…",Celestebyrne3,USA,['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPad,172,679,2020-07-12 17:38:24,False,"[('Friday', 'DATE'), ('the Ohio Department of Health', 'ORG'), ('62,856', 'CARDINAL'), '', ('8,701', 'CARDINAL'), ('3,032 dea', 'QUANTITY')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
82,, Germany and UK have similar population densities. Germany has a slightly higher population.#Coronavirus deaths in Germ…,Mortimer4Kim,Romsey,['Coronavirus'],Twitter for iPad,541,220,2020-07-12 17:38:24,False,"[('Germany', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Germany', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
83,, Trump wearing the mask like thisEffective? 🙄🙄😂😂😂😂😂😷😷😷😷😷#Covid_19 #coronavirus ,akasha2458,Illinois,"['Covid_19', 'coronavirus']",Twitter Web App,853,896,2020-07-12 17:38:23,False,"[('🙄🙄', 'FAC'), ('😷', 'CARDINAL'), ('😷', 'CARDINAL'), ('😷', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.737, 'pos': 0.263, 'compound': 0.3612}"
84,," . orders ""his representatives"" to back off from questioning or impeaching  ! Asks people to help o…",Mira63330096,,[],Twitter for Android,1138,872,2020-07-12 17:38:22,False,[],"{'neg': 0.08, 'neu': 0.747, 'pos': 0.172, 'compound': 0.3802}"
85,, This from 2017 remains true: Betsy Devos is more of a danger to students than a silly old bear. Remember she wanted to arm…,Frustratedlady3,,[],Twitter for iPhone,70,38,2020-07-12 17:38:21,False,"[('2017', 'DATE'), ('Betsy Devos', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.138, 'neu': 0.715, 'pos': 0.147, 'compound': -0.197}"
86,,"It's NOT safe in any public places.#coronavirus #COVID19 has spreaded ALL OVER.People and state govenors didn't take the virus seriously.ALL we heard was ""OPEN UP""A directive fromDonald Trump &amp; his campaign team.What is the DEATH COUNT today??#Florida#Texas ",jenniferclmn,"Virginia, USA","['coronavirus', 'COVID19', 'Florida', 'Texas']",Twitter for Android,1173,341,2020-07-12 17:38:20,False,"[('COVID19', 'ORG'), ('OPEN', 'ORG'), ('Trump &amp', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.175, 'neu': 0.825, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8126}"
87,,Faite vous livrer en mp surSnapchat: plugstore19 Wickr me: plugshopping19 #lausanne #coronavirus #cougars #gays #londres #london #paris2020 #greve #gayparis #weedsmokers ,claver420,"Tremblay-en-France, France  , ","['lausanne', 'coronavirus', 'cougars', 'gays', 'londres', 'london', 'paris2020', 'greve', 'gayparis', 'weedsmokers']",Twitter for Android,33,30,2020-07-12 17:38:18,False,"['', '', '', '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
88,, India reaches on 8th rank in world in terms of death due to Corona and still BJP Govt is claiming that they faught Coron…,SinghRiya17,,[],Twitter for Android,79,112,2020-07-12 17:38:18,False,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('8th', 'ORDINAL'), ('Corona', 'GPE'), ('BJP Govt', 'ORG'), ('Coron', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.144, 'neu': 0.812, 'pos': 0.044, 'compound': -0.5719}"
89,," . is releasing 8,000 inmates due to #coronavirus fears! 🤬 I’m fed up with his “leadership.” I’m seriously cons…",KingTigerII1,,['coronavirus'],Twitter for Android,15,223,2020-07-12 17:38:17,False,"[('8,000', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.242, 'neu': 0.758, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5848}"
90,,  #CoronaVirus Biggest psyop in human history! What is the difference when testing for #COVID19 compared to…,ColeenSwartzen1,,"['CoronaVirus', 'COVID19']",Twitter for iPhone,231,627,2020-07-12 17:38:16,False,"['', ('CoronaVirus Biggest', 'ORG'), ('COVID19', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
91,," . is releasing 8,000 inmates due to #coronavirus fears! 🤬 I’m fed up with his “leadership.” I’m seriously cons…",lunch_joe,California,['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPad,12865,13542,2020-07-12 17:38:16,False,"[('8,000', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.242, 'neu': 0.758, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5848}"
92,," It's just a start, they were threatening and war mongering a few weeks back against #india #usa #Australia #uk #canada china should be punished for it's atrocities against #Uyghurs  #HongKong #taiwan and hiding facts on #coronavirus . Dragon wings clipped #chinawingsclipped",gokusingh123,Ladakh,"['india', 'usa', 'Australia', 'uk', 'canada', 'Uyghurs', 'HongKong', 'taiwan', 'coronavirus', 'chinawingsclipped']",Twitter Web App,12,180,2020-07-12 17:38:15,False,"[('a few weeks', 'DATE'), '', '', '', ('canada', 'GPE'), ('china', 'GPE'), ('Uyghurs', 'ORG'), '', ('taiwan', 'GPE'), '', '']","{'neg': 0.302, 'neu': 0.698, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.9231}"
93,," Tomorrow isn’t promised, Just let him fucc.#coronavirus",slimm_kole,"New Orleans, LA",['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPhone,255,692,2020-07-12 17:38:15,False,"[('Tomorrow', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.706, 'pos': 0.294, 'compound': 0.3612}"
94,,"  Betsy Devos can maintain social distancing on her 163 ft yacht, while she wants children to be forced to return to sc…",CommonCores,,[],Twitter Web App,10835,11,2020-07-12 17:38:15,False,"[('Betsy Devos', 'PERSON'), ('163', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.125, 'neu': 0.875, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4588}"
95,, Breaking: Aishwarya Rai Bachhan and her daughter Tested Positive For Coronavirus.#coronavirus #AmitabhBachchan #Abhi…,Shubham84865021,,"['coronavirus', 'AmitabhBachchan']",Twitter for Android,8,880,2020-07-12 17:38:14,False,"[('Aishwarya Rai Bachhan', 'PERSON'), ('Tested Positive', 'ORG'), ('AmitabhBachchan', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.769, 'pos': 0.231, 'compound': 0.5574}"
96,," . is releasing 8,000 inmates due to #coronavirus fears! 🤬 I’m fed up with his “leadership.” I’m seriously cons…",joshallen961,Kekistan,['coronavirus'],Twitter Web App,7,24,2020-07-12 17:38:12,False,"[('8,000', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.242, 'neu': 0.758, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5848}"
98,,"Florida just reported a record 15,300 new #coronavirus cases, the most by any state in a single day since the pandemic hit the U.S. That’s how not under control this thing is.Meanwhile, millions of kids are supposed to go back to school in 6 weeks? ",derekjGZ,"Washington, DC",['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPhone,38581,1865,2020-07-12 17:38:11,True,"[('Florida', 'GPE'), ('15,300', 'CARDINAL'), ('a single day', 'DATE'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('6 weeks', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
99,,  Nope! I don't believe death rate either because people who died of other causes are being listed as #ChinaVirus d…,TheOneLadyEagle,,['ChinaVirus'],Twitter Web App,14032,13585,2020-07-12 17:38:11,False,[''],"{'neg': 0.276, 'neu': 0.724, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.7565}"
100,,"Florida reported more than 15,000 new #coronavirus cases, the highest single-day total for any state — including New York — since the pandemic began. ",enjoyceinglife,"The ATL, baby...","['coronavirus', 'COVID19']",Twitter Web App,3349,4126,2020-07-12 17:38:11,False,"[('Florida', 'GPE'), ('more than 15,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('single-day', 'DATE'), ('New York', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
101,, Disney World’s grand re-opening announcement video seems WAY more appropriate with the theme from the Shining. #Covid19 #Co…,NaattuVarthakal,കേരളം,['Covid19'],Naattuvartha,2868,4701,2020-07-12 17:38:10,False,"[('Disney World', 'ORG'), ('WAY', 'ORG'), ('Shining', 'PRODUCT'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.85, 'pos': 0.15, 'compound': 0.4588}"
102,," 🚨BREAKING: #Florida reports a staggering 15,300 new #coronavirus cases, shattering the single-day record of any state—pr…",blank3nsoap,"Mount Vernon, IN","['Florida', 'coronavirus']",Twitter for iPhone,38,302,2020-07-12 17:38:10,False,"[('Florida', 'GPE'), ('15,300', 'CARDINAL'), ('the single-day', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
103,, Russia first nation to successfully complete human trials of #coronavirus #COVID19 vaccine,lakshmisurendra,Bangalore,"['coronavirus', 'COVID19']",Twitter for iPhone,62,373,2020-07-12 17:38:10,False,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), '', '', ('COVID19', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.775, 'pos': 0.225, 'compound': 0.4939}"
104,, Disney World’s grand re-opening announcement video seems WAY more appropriate with the theme from the Shining. #Covid19 #Co…,dannielynnbowie,,['Covid19'],Twitter for iPhone,12,25,2020-07-12 17:38:09,False,"[('Disney World', 'ORG'), ('WAY', 'ORG'), ('Shining', 'PRODUCT'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.85, 'pos': 0.15, 'compound': 0.4588}"
105,,". 71 tested positive and you have a guy wearing no PPE, wearing SHORTS disinfecting the whole field? Did he sign up for death?? He will have cancer within two years, but you got to play your stupid game and make your money. #coronavirus I hope it was worth it. ",cwalshCURO,Southern California | Sweden,['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPad,1922,4974,2020-07-12 17:38:08,False,"[('71', 'CARDINAL'), ('two years', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.182, 'neu': 0.624, 'pos': 0.194, 'compound': 0.1999}"
106,, Air India announces 14 more flights between India and UK under Vande Bharat Mission | via  #AirIndia #VandeBh…,JTVIndiaNews,,['AirIndia'],Twitter for Android,244,49,2020-07-12 17:38:08,False,"[('Air India', 'ORG'), ('14', 'CARDINAL'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Vande Bharat Mission |', 'LAW'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
107,, ‼️37-year-old #Ohio veteran—who posted a widely shared anti-#mask screed on Facebook—tested positive for #COVID19 on Jul…,albinojiginosis,"Rockford, IL","['Ohio', 'mask', 'COVID19']",Twitter for Android,206,284,2020-07-12 17:38:07,False,"[('Ohio', 'GPE'), ('Facebook', 'ORG'), ('Jul', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.684, 'pos': 0.316, 'compound': 0.7184}"
108,, Are young people at fault for the rise in #coronavirus cases in many states across the U.S.? spoke with …,ItsmeSriram,Bangalore,['coronavirus'],Twitter for Android,163,241,2020-07-12 17:38:07,False,"['', ('U.S.', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.13, 'neu': 0.87, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4019}"
109,," Remaining home and avoiding external exposure, unless critical, are KEY to staying off #coronavirus. Kindly follow this.…",DrRajbangshi,,['coronavirus'],Twitter for Android,290,222,2020-07-12 17:38:07,False,"[('KEY', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.215, 'neu': 0.639, 'pos': 0.146, 'compound': -0.128}"
110,, 15 recent flights in and out of Toronto have confirmed cases of COVID-19 ,JaniceKayePhD,Canada,"['Toronto', 'Coronavirus', 'COVID19']",Twitter Web App,771,858,2020-07-12 17:38:07,False,"[('15', 'CARDINAL'), ('Toronto', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
111,, Today MSDH is reporting 868 new cases of COVID-19 in Mississippi and 19 deaths. The total of #coronavirus cases since March 11 is…,Shaye_Tova,"Call me what you want, but put Dr. first. ",['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPhone,708,946,2020-07-12 17:38:07,False,"[('Today', 'DATE'), ('MSDH', 'ORG'), ('868', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mississippi', 'GPE'), ('19', 'CARDINAL'), '', ('March 11', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
112,," . is releasing 8,000 inmates due to #coronavirus fears! 🤬 I’m fed up with his “leadership.” I’m seriously cons…",ghostwolfman,"NB /DC, Maine, USA/Canada ",['coronavirus'],Twitter Web App,27961,28975,2020-07-12 17:38:07,False,"[('8,000', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.242, 'neu': 0.758, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5848}"
113,,"With #COVID19 on my mind, I decided to make #coronavirus inspired chocolate covered cherries. ",cemccarthy02,"Rockville, MD","['COVID19', 'coronavirus']",Twitter for iPhone,1656,1935,2020-07-12 17:38:06,False,"['', '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.789, 'pos': 0.211, 'compound': 0.4939}"
114,,Looks like the #coronavirus just requested to follow my Instagram.... 😗🙄Seems legit ,bachgenbachx,"Wales, United Kingdom",['coronavirus'],Twitter for Android,1466,282,2020-07-12 17:38:05,False,"['', ('Instagram', 'PRODUCT'), ('😗', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.815, 'pos': 0.185, 'compound': 0.3612}"
115,,  mask is 1 step. Want to try to muster more votes? #LetFauciLead to finally control this #coronavirus. To seek his expert guidance would be a positive for u. Wish you’d understand he is not in competition w u. His focus: humanitarian wellbeing.  #sundayvibes,AMouseRoars,,"['LetFauciLead', 'coronavirus', 'sundayvibes']",Twitter for iPhone,5,60,2020-07-12 17:38:05,False,"[('1', 'CARDINAL'), '', ('Wish', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.83, 'pos': 0.17, 'compound': 0.765}"
116,," SOME CONTEXT: #FL set records today. Best testing done, the % positive is ⬇️, plus 15,300 new #coronavirus cases is the M…",trekinfl,,"['FL', 'coronavirus']",Twitter for iPad,124,739,2020-07-12 17:38:05,False,"['', ('FL', 'NORP'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('15,300', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.709, 'pos': 0.291, 'compound': 0.8316}"
117,," please make it mandatory to wear masks in shops and enclosed spaces, follow #spain as they are on top of #coronavirus. Nothing worse when in a shop and someone coughs or sneezes and they don’t have a mask 😷 on!!!",Chrisman51,"Broadstairs,Kent UK","['spain', 'coronavirus']",Twitter for iPhone,766,1016,2020-07-12 17:38:04,False,"[('spain', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.789, 'pos': 0.211, 'compound': 0.7802}"
118,," 🚨BREAKING: #Florida reports a staggering 15,300 new #coronavirus cases, shattering the single-day record of any state—pr…",facelift25,Alive in the Superunknown,"['Florida', 'coronavirus']",Twitter Web App,336,1926,2020-07-12 17:38:03,False,"[('Florida', 'GPE'), ('15,300', 'CARDINAL'), ('the single-day', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
119,,RT copy  FDA approved plasma treatment for sickest #coronavirus patients &gt;&gt;&gt;  via  &gt;&gt;&gt; #HealthTech #COVID19 &gt;&gt;&gt; ,cyber_spanish,Spain,"['coronavirus', 'HealthTech', 'COVID19']",Twitter Web App,4382,4230,2020-07-12 17:38:03,False,"[('FDA', 'ORG'), '', ('coronavirus patients &gt;&gt;&gt', 'ORG'), ('HealthTech', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.843, 'pos': 0.157, 'compound': 0.4215}"
120,, Due to #COVID19 aka #Coronavirus Ill be sending the first 900 people to like &amp; retweet this $300 -$1500 through CashAp…,bellafeetsbaby,,"['COVID19', 'Coronavirus']",Twitter for iPhone,3,51,2020-07-12 17:38:02,False,"['', '', ('Coronavirus Ill', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('&amp', 'ORG'), ('300', 'MONEY'), ('CashAp', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.115, 'neu': 0.782, 'pos': 0.103, 'compound': -0.0772}"
121,, Russia first nation to successfully complete human trials of #coronavirus #COVID19 vaccine,BeingBanna7773,वीर भूमि राजस्थान,"['coronavirus', 'COVID19']",Twitter for Android,70,459,2020-07-12 17:38:02,False,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), '', '', ('COVID19', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.775, 'pos': 0.225, 'compound': 0.4939}"
122,," This just in: Florida reports 15,000 new #coronavirus cases. Shattering records are you, ?",deeg13,Massachusetts,['coronavirus'],Twitter Web App,2615,3025,2020-07-12 17:38:02,False,"[('Florida', 'GPE'), ('15,000', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
123,," Florida posts over 15,000 new cases of #coronavirus At the same time, countless GOPers are refusing to cooperate in slow…",406Llama,"Montana, USA",['coronavirus'],Twitter Web App,1541,3726,2020-07-12 17:38:01,False,"[('Florida', 'GPE'), ('over 15,000', 'CARDINAL'), '', ('GOPers', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.124, 'neu': 0.876, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4019}"
124,,Our #pandemic response is stalling. And it’s made worse by #Trump’s ignorance. ,SoCalDoc,SoCal,"['pandemic', 'Trump', 'Coronavirus', 'covid19', 'DumpTrump2020']",Buffer,302,295,2020-07-12 17:38:00,False,"['', ('Trump', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.451, 'neu': 0.549, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.7506}"
125,, Democrats reviewing their platform #Trump2020LandslideVictory #KAG2020 #Tcot #Ccot#COVID19 #coronavirus #WalkAway #Saturday…,88DPD88,"Mesa, AZ","['Trump2020LandslideVictory', 'KAG2020', 'Tcot', 'Ccot', 'COVID19', 'coronavirus', 'WalkAway']",Twitter for Android,3047,4584,2020-07-12 17:38:00,False,"[('Democrats', 'NORP'), ('Ccot#COVID19', 'ORG'), '', ('Saturday', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
126,,Bitter truth !! 🙄#coronavirus#PrayForAll#CoronaVirusUpdates #CoronavirusOutbreak ,Amiable_leo,,"['coronavirus', 'PrayForAll', 'CoronaVirusUpdates', 'CoronavirusOutbreak']",Twitter for Android,9,178,2020-07-12 17:38:00,False,[],"{'neg': 0.39, 'neu': 0.345, 'pos': 0.265, 'compound': -0.2695}"
127,,"Stay alert to the symptoms of #coronavirus. You should self-isolate and book a test if you experience:– a loss or change in sense of smell or taste– a high temperature – a new, continuous cough Book a test: ",NHSEnglandLDN,"London, England",['coronavirus'],Twitter Media Studio,94705,5477,2020-07-12 17:38:00,True,[],"{'neg': 0.067, 'neu': 0.87, 'pos': 0.064, 'compound': -0.0258}"
128,," Tomorrow isn’t promised, Just let him fucc.#coronavirus",xxxTha_Dreamxxx,"St Louis, MO",['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPhone,471,262,2020-07-12 17:37:59,False,"[('Tomorrow', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.706, 'pos': 0.294, 'compound': 0.3612}"
129,," This is a certain group of white people sympathetic to his tapestry of white power going gaga over small things, plain and simple #coronavirus #WhiteSupremacy",_quark_,San Francisco,"['coronavirus', 'WhiteSupremacy']",Twitter for Android,1789,1781,2020-07-12 17:37:58,False,"['', ('WhiteSupremacy', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.803, 'pos': 0.197, 'compound': 0.6597}"
130,," For over a decade, 's #FeedSoCal program has been supporting our local #foodbanks, but now because of the #coronavi…",erijlulu,South Cali,"['FeedSoCal', 'foodbanks']",Twitter for iPhone,21,148,2020-07-12 17:37:58,False,"['', '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.897, 'pos': 0.103, 'compound': 0.2382}"
131,,#Pune #PCMC Are Lockdowns effective in reducing #coronavirus cases...? ,w_karve,,"['Pune', 'PCMC', 'coronavirus']",Twitter for Android,4426,2881,2020-07-12 17:37:57,False,"[('PCMC', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.721, 'pos': 0.279, 'compound': 0.4767}"
132,," . is releasing 8,000 inmates due to #coronavirus fears! 🤬 I’m fed up with his “leadership.” I’m seriously cons…",RTR_Chris,"Birmingham, AL",['coronavirus'],Twitter for Android,3096,3584,2020-07-12 17:37:56,False,"[('8,000', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.242, 'neu': 0.758, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5848}"
133,, ‼️37-year-old #Ohio veteran—who posted a widely shared anti-#mask screed on Facebook—tested positive for #COVID19 on Jul…,SPEAKUPJULIA,Red State,"['Ohio', 'mask', 'COVID19']",Twitter for Android,7422,6875,2020-07-12 17:37:55,False,"[('Ohio', 'GPE'), ('Facebook', 'ORG'), ('Jul', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.684, 'pos': 0.316, 'compound': 0.7184}"
134,," More than 69,300 people have died of the novel #coronavirus in 342 cities checkered across all of Iran's 31 provinces, ac…",manzarbokharai,Sverige,['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPhone,235,179,2020-07-12 17:37:54,False,"[('342', 'CARDINAL'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('31', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.145, 'neu': 0.763, 'pos': 0.092, 'compound': -0.3182}"
135,,Mask protection efficiency 😷 🦠 #coronavirus #COVIDー19 #الكورونا #Algerie ,imenmess27,Alger                         ,"['coronavirus', 'COVIDー19', 'الكورونا', 'Algerie']",Twitter for iPhone,296,728,2020-07-12 17:37:54,False,"[('😷', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.706, 'pos': 0.294, 'compound': 0.3612}"
136,, Every American death from #coronavirus is the result of the futile opposition of the radical Democrats who tried to dete…,Artemiss1990,#persia,['coronavirus'],Twitter for Android,400,475,2020-07-12 17:37:52,False,"[('American', 'NORP'), ('Democrats', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.274, 'neu': 0.726, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.7783}"
137,, Russia completes trials of world's first COVID-19 vaccine. #COVID19 #coronavirus #CoronavirusPandemic #corona #COVID2019 #t…,moemin71180617,,"['COVID19', 'coronavirus', 'CoronavirusPandemic', 'corona', 'COVID2019']",Twitter for Android,67,287,2020-07-12 17:37:50,False,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), '', '', ('CoronavirusPandemic', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
138,, This is the highest single-day total for any US state since the start of the #coronavirus pandemic.,opedwriter,,['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPhone,1482,1417,2020-07-12 17:37:50,False,"[('US', 'GPE'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
139,," TRACKING COVID-19: Nevada is reporting 845 new COVID-19 cases as more than 9,000 tests were conducted statewide in the past 2…",DrKavarga,"Las Vegas, NV",[],Twitter Web App,2300,4992,2020-07-12 17:37:49,False,"[('TRACKING', 'ORG'), ('Nevada', 'GPE'), ('845', 'CARDINAL'), ('more than 9,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('2', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
140,, I almost forgot the faces of people without masks😞#coronavirus #sundayvibes ,Toma176589237,,"['coronavirus', 'sundayvibes']",Twitter for Android,78,186,2020-07-12 17:37:48,False,[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
141,,"💕It's the #Souls, #Minds &amp; #hearts we touch💕💕 with #Love that will measure our #Success!💕   #LoveTRAINFROMIRAN #JOYtrain #successTRAIN #GoldenHearts #starfishclub #IRAN #IRANIAN #IAM #coronavirus #IAMChoosingLove #chooselove #sundayvibes #BeKind #kindness ",Bijan_Cyrus,"Iran,Tehran & The Persian Gulf","['Souls', 'Minds', 'hearts', 'Love', 'Success', 'LoveTRAINFROMIRAN', 'JOYtrain', 'successTRAIN', 'GoldenHearts', 'starfishclub', 'IRAN', 'IRANIAN', 'IAM', 'coronavirus', 'IAMChoosingLove', 'chooselove', 'sundayvibes', 'BeKind', 'kindness']",Twitter Web App,2322,1954,2020-07-12 17:37:48,False,"[('Souls', 'GPE'), '', ('Minds &amp', 'ORG'), ('💕💕', 'CARDINAL'), ('Success', 'ORG'), ('💕', 'CARDINAL'), '', ('GoldenHearts', 'ORG'), '', '', '', '', '', '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
142,,"Another Trump, the #DumbestPresidentEver, kisser   threatens schools to reopen in this Fall.Invest school safety measures to protect students; teachers; and others from contracting #coronavirus.  is trying to  spread  #coronavirus more.",amyadams100,California,"['DumbestPresidentEver', 'coronavirus', 'coronavirus']",Twitter for iPhone,5,10,2020-07-12 17:37:48,False,"[('DumbestPresidentEver', 'MONEY'), ('this Fall', 'DATE'), '', '']","{'neg': 0.071, 'neu': 0.708, 'pos': 0.221, 'compound': 0.6705}"
143,," Why has #AmitabhBachchan admitted himself to hospital after being #COVID19 positive? What happened to his 'Taali, Shankh' the…",RafaqatSapra,Lahore,"['AmitabhBachchan', 'COVID19']",Twitter for iPad,1806,2256,2020-07-12 17:37:47,False,"['', ('AmitabhBachchan', 'ORG'), ('Taali', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.762, 'pos': 0.238, 'compound': 0.6124}"
144,, Do you think lockdown should be reimposed to stop the rise of COVID-19 cases in Telangana?#Telangana #coronavirus #loc…,sayedafatima19,,"['Telangana', 'coronavirus']",Twitter for Android,1,10,2020-07-12 17:37:47,False,[''],"{'neg': 0.115, 'neu': 0.885, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.296}"
145,," Internal documents from  warned fully reopening K-12 schools &amp; universities would pose the ""highest risk"" for spread of the…",STabbytosavit,"Tehachapi, Calif.",[],Twitter Web App,31866,31844,2020-07-12 17:37:46,False,"[('K-12', 'PRODUCT')]","{'neg': 0.198, 'neu': 0.802, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4939}"
146,," Iran: Coronavirus Update, Over 69,800 Deaths, July 12, 2020, 6:00 PM CESTThe People’s Mojahedin Organization of Iran (PMO…",Mohamma28307078,,[],Twitter for iPhone,103,34,2020-07-12 17:37:46,False,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Deaths', 'PERSON'), ('July 12, 2020', 'DATE'), ('6:00 PM', 'TIME'), ('People’s Mojahedin Organization of Iran', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
147,," So it looks like the GOP's strategy to use the #coronavirus pandemic as a holocaust against POCs, old folks, disabled f…",JonS253,,['coronavirus'],Twitter for Android,590,196,2020-07-12 17:37:45,False,"[('GOP', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.873, 'pos': 0.127, 'compound': 0.4144}"
148,," 🚨BREAKING: #Florida reports a staggering 15,300 new #coronavirus cases, shattering the single-day record of any state—pr…",krkhawk,,"['Florida', 'coronavirus']",Twitter for iPhone,31,104,2020-07-12 17:37:45,False,"[('Florida', 'GPE'), ('15,300', 'CARDINAL'), ('the single-day', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
149,," . is releasing 8,000 inmates due to #coronavirus fears! 🤬 I’m fed up with his “leadership.” I’m seriously cons…",veram43395421,,['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPhone,5329,4981,2020-07-12 17:37:45,False,"[('8,000', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.242, 'neu': 0.758, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5848}"
150,," . is releasing 8,000 inmates due to #coronavirus fears! 🤬 I’m fed up with his “leadership.” I’m seriously cons…",jack_20141009,,['coronavirus'],Twitter for Android,2381,3609,2020-07-12 17:37:45,False,"[('8,000', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.242, 'neu': 0.758, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5848}"
151,, #China is suspending imports of #meat and meat products from 23 companies and stepping-up inspection of imported foods…,rsh17d_r,United States,"['China', 'meat']",Twitter for iPhone,115,327,2020-07-12 17:37:44,False,"['', ('China', 'GPE'), ('23', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
152,," BREAKING: Florida smashes record for daily new #coronavirus cases with the FL Dept of Health reporting 15,300 new cases tod…",AlexBrooklyn14,,['coronavirus'],Twitter for Android,211,1823,2020-07-12 17:37:43,False,"[('BREAKING', 'PERSON'), ('Florida', 'GPE'), ('daily', 'DATE'), '', ('the FL Dept of Health', 'ORG'), ('15,300', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
153,, Homemade pastry.Corona makes me bake sweets.#SundayMotivation #coronavirus ,Toma176589237,,"['SundayMotivation', 'coronavirus']",Twitter for Android,78,186,2020-07-12 17:37:43,False,"[('Homemade', 'PERSON'), ('Corona', 'PERSON'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
154,," Covid-19 is not the only disease that can be avoided with better hygiene, face masks and social distancing. Learn how to s…",DeborahDian,"Orange County, California",[],Twitter for Android,5207,5729,2020-07-12 17:37:42,False,[],"{'neg': 0.095, 'neu': 0.791, 'pos': 0.115, 'compound': 0.128}"
155,, Reopened schools in Europe and Asia have largely avoided #coronavirus outbreaks. They have important lessons to teach u…,KLScottBarber,"Toronto, Ontario",['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPad,32,156,2020-07-12 17:37:42,False,"[('Reopened', 'PERSON'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Asia', 'LOC'), '']","{'neg': 0.119, 'neu': 0.792, 'pos': 0.089, 'compound': -0.1531}"
156,, Due to #COVID19 aka #Coronavirus Ill be sending the first 500 people to like &amp; retweet this $1500-$3500  through CashA…,levantebriggs01,,"['COVID19', 'Coronavirus']",Twitter for iPhone,443,382,2020-07-12 17:37:42,False,"['', '', ('Coronavirus Ill', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('500', 'CARDINAL'), ('&amp', 'ORG'), ('1500-$3500', 'MONEY')]","{'neg': 0.12, 'neu': 0.773, 'pos': 0.107, 'compound': -0.0772}"
157,," Internal documents from  warned fully reopening K-12 schools &amp; universities would pose the ""highest risk"" for spread of the…",ANN13951880,"Ohio, USA",[],Twitter Web App,608,688,2020-07-12 17:37:41,False,"[('K-12', 'PRODUCT')]","{'neg': 0.198, 'neu': 0.802, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4939}"
158,," . is releasing 8,000 inmates due to #coronavirus fears! 🤬 I’m fed up with his “leadership.” I’m seriously cons…",ReneeMetcalf13,,['coronavirus'],Twitter for Android,3955,4834,2020-07-12 17:37:40,False,"[('8,000', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.242, 'neu': 0.758, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5848}"
159,," The UK death toll now stands at 44,819 #coronavirus",ANDYC2311,London & Woking (from Leeds!),['coronavirus'],Twitter for Android,2372,5001,2020-07-12 17:37:40,False,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('44,819 #coronavirus', 'QUANTITY')]","{'neg': 0.328, 'neu': 0.672, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5994}"
160,," While the #coronavirus pandemic has put restrictions on many aspects of peoples’ everyday lives, one area that it seems…",puputrossi,"ÜT: -6.235204,106.797529",['coronavirus'],Twitter for Android,919,951,2020-07-12 17:37:39,False,"['', ('one', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
161,," . is releasing 8,000 inmates due to #coronavirus fears! 🤬 I’m fed up with his “leadership.” I’m seriously cons…",Christi44543430,,['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPhone,67,213,2020-07-12 17:37:39,False,"[('8,000', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.242, 'neu': 0.758, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5848}"
162,," Coronavirus in Louisiana: State reports 1,319 new cases, 13 new deaths on Sunday -- ",__itsque,"Fuck Da Police, Louisiana",['LocalNews'],Twitter for iPhone,1409,1405,2020-07-12 17:37:38,False,"[('Coronavirus', 'NORP'), ('Louisiana', 'GPE'), ('1,319', 'CARDINAL'), ('13', 'CARDINAL'), ('Sunday', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
163,, BENGALURU #COVIDー19 STATUS🚑 Sunday -1525 +ve (Chennai -1168)Saturday -1533 +ve (Chennai -1185)Friday -1447 +ve (Chennai…,edsudhir,bangalore,['COVIDー19'],Twitter for iPhone,401,3507,2020-07-12 17:37:38,False,"[('BENGALURU', 'ORG'), ('Chennai', 'MONEY'), ('Chennai', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
164,, Coronavirus: Why everyone was wrong--The immune response to the virus is stronger than everyone thought,blueBooBooBear,"California, USA",[],Twitter Web App,1195,747,2020-07-12 17:37:37,False,"[('Coronavirus', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.73, 'pos': 0.27, 'compound': 0.5859}"
165,,#ThingsToDo during the #CoronaVirus #Quarantine. Number 27.  Buy yourself a mini-laser and start etching cool pics into your stuff.  The ultimate in personalization!  (GiGadgets) #Technology ,jamesvgingerich,"Waterloo, Ontario Canada","['ThingsToDo', 'CoronaVirus', 'Quarantine', 'Technology']",TweetDeck,44082,43637,2020-07-12 17:37:36,False,"['', ('CoronaVirus', 'ORG'), ('Quarantine', 'PRODUCT'), ('27', 'CARDINAL'), ('GiGadgets', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.85, 'pos': 0.15, 'compound': 0.4389}"
166,, British holidaymakers travelling to Ireland will continue to be subject to quarantine as the Dublin government seeks to avoid…,DebbieG03792452,,[],Twitter for Android,40,320,2020-07-12 17:37:36,False,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Ireland', 'GPE'), ('Dublin', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
167,, 🔴 Watch: #Coronavirus is leading many people to consider making #aliyah. Here's how to find the perfect home in Israel.…,doctorreemah,New York City,"['Coronavirus', 'aliyah']",Twitter Web App,87,450,2020-07-12 17:37:35,False,"['', ('Coronavirus', 'PRODUCT'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.829, 'pos': 0.171, 'compound': 0.5719}"
168,," Instead of issuing cruel threats to the well-being of the most vulnerable students, this Administration should be doing eve…",beemeander,Seattle,[],Twitter Web App,2992,4998,2020-07-12 17:37:34,False,[],"{'neg': 0.355, 'neu': 0.645, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8313}"
169,," . is releasing 8,000 inmates due to #coronavirus fears! 🤬 I’m fed up with his “leadership.” I’m seriously cons…",Ru4jones,"Ohio, USA",['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPhone,365,2136,2020-07-12 17:37:33,False,"[('8,000', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.242, 'neu': 0.758, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5848}"
170,,"No shit LA lost control early while the contagion spread wildly: ""A county memo asked hospitals to turn away any suspected #coronavirus patient with mild symptoms — without a test and without reporting the case."" ",NicoletteGlazer,"Century City, California",['coronavirus'],Twitter for Android,14467,8005,2020-07-12 17:37:33,False,"[('LA', 'GPE'), '']","{'neg': 0.317, 'neu': 0.683, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.9001}"
171,, The Emperor has no mask.#coronavirus,DonNadon9,"Ontario, Canada",['coronavirus'],Twitter for Android,668,1264,2020-07-12 17:37:32,False,[],"{'neg': 0.355, 'neu': 0.645, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.296}"
172,, Trump wearing the mask like thisEffective? 🙄🙄😂😂😂😂😂😷😷😷😷😷#Covid_19 #coronavirus ,PLapann,,"['Covid_19', 'coronavirus']",Twitter Web App,352,418,2020-07-12 17:37:30,False,"[('🙄🙄', 'FAC'), ('😷', 'CARDINAL'), ('😷', 'CARDINAL'), ('😷', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.737, 'pos': 0.263, 'compound': 0.3612}"
173,," . is releasing 8,000 inmates due to #coronavirus fears! 🤬 I’m fed up with his “leadership.” I’m seriously cons…",KDonahay,,['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPad,457,749,2020-07-12 17:37:30,False,"[('8,000', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.242, 'neu': 0.758, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5848}"
174,, 🔴 Watch: #Coronavirus is leading many people to consider making #aliyah. Here's how to find the perfect home in Israel.…,covid19_alerts,"Westmont, IL","['Coronavirus', 'aliyah']",Microsoft Power Platform,195,126,2020-07-12 17:37:30,False,"['', ('Coronavirus', 'PRODUCT'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.829, 'pos': 0.171, 'compound': 0.5719}"
175,," . is releasing 8,000 inmates due to #coronavirus fears! 🤬 I’m fed up with his “leadership.” I’m seriously cons…",covid19_alerts,"Westmont, IL",['coronavirus'],Microsoft Power Platform,195,126,2020-07-12 17:37:30,False,"[('8,000', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.242, 'neu': 0.758, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5848}"
176,, The Honduras #sugar industry continues to do its part in helping people during the #coronavirus pandemic. Another example th…,marcelolacayo13,Tegucigalpa-Honduras,"['sugar', 'coronavirus']",Twitter for iPhone,258,198,2020-07-12 17:37:28,False,"[('Honduras', 'GPE'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.891, 'pos': 0.109, 'compound': 0.296}"
177,, 🚨BREAKING: Commissioner in #Florida who *voted against #masks* has tested positive for #COVID19 and is currently in the…,yiffens,philly/miami,"['Florida', 'masks', 'COVID19']",Twitter for Android,18,115,2020-07-12 17:37:28,False,"[('Florida', 'GPE'), '', '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.825, 'pos': 0.175, 'compound': 0.5574}"
178,, Today’s #COVID19 in 🇨🇦 info and updates:➡️#GOC website on #coronavirus disease: ➡️COVID-19 Situ…,johangreg,"Calgary, Alberta","['COVID19', 'GOC', 'coronavirus']",Twitter for iPhone,3295,1220,2020-07-12 17:37:28,False,"[('Today', 'DATE'), '', ('➡', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
179,," Censorship is the #quarantine of thought!And when thought is quarantined, as it doesn't die, it will be transmitted to…",Artemiss1990,#persia,['quarantine'],Twitter for Android,400,475,2020-07-12 17:37:27,False,[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.84, 'pos': 0.16, 'compound': 0.5327}"
180,, 🔴 Watch: #Coronavirus is leading many people to consider making #aliyah. Here's how to find the perfect home in Israel.…,MonarchinMN,"International Falls, MN","['Coronavirus', 'aliyah']",Twitter for Android,675,542,2020-07-12 17:37:27,False,"['', ('Coronavirus', 'PRODUCT'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.829, 'pos': 0.171, 'compound': 0.5719}"
181,, #Qanon #WWGIWGA #Coronavirus MASKS ARE A SCAM AND DO NOT WORK ,joa_2020,,"['Qanon', 'WWGIWGA', 'Coronavirus']",Twitter Web App,582,783,2020-07-12 17:37:27,False,"['', ('WWGIWGA', 'ORG'), ('Coronavirus MASKS', 'ORG'), ('SCAM', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.33, 'neu': 0.67, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6633}"
182,,"Top story: : 'WATCH: President Donald Trump wears a mask during a scheduled visit to the Walter Reed National Military Medical Center, a rare instance of doing so publicly as #coronavirus cases continue to pil… ",Gates_Ventures,"Portland, Oregon, USA",['coronavirus'],The Tweeted Times,6039,2860,2020-07-12 17:37:27,False,"[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('the Walter Reed National Military Medical Center', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.943, 'pos': 0.057, 'compound': 0.2023}"
183,," . is releasing 8,000 inmates due to #coronavirus fears! 🤬 I’m fed up with his “leadership.” I’m seriously cons…",NPJules,"Kansas City, MO",['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPhone,6876,7442,2020-07-12 17:37:26,False,"[('8,000', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.242, 'neu': 0.758, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5848}"
184,, DeSantis is nothing more than #tRumpLite This is what their denial produces. #coronavirus disease and death ,AdamAddict,In Nirvana on Venus,"['tRumpLite', 'coronavirus']",Twitter for Android,2582,1274,2020-07-12 17:37:26,False,"[('DeSantis', 'PERSON'), ('more than #', 'MONEY'), '']","{'neg': 0.206, 'neu': 0.794, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5994}"
185,, #tomhanks #Johnpodesta #FRAZZLEDRIP #pizzagatelsreal #pizzagate #obama #tonypodesta #TrumpHasNoCredibility #coronavirus #Hil…,William__Haddad,"Rancho Cucamonga, CA","['tomhanks', 'Johnpodesta', 'FRAZZLEDRIP', 'pizzagatelsreal', 'pizzagate', 'obama', 'tonypodesta', 'TrumpHasNoCredibility', 'coronavirus']",Twitter for iPhone,201,295,2020-07-12 17:37:24,False,"['', ('Johnpodesta', 'NORP'), '', '', '', ('Hil', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
186,, The President has been a complete failure in dealing with the #coronavirus and now he’s messing with our children’s health.…,skaik_van,Ohio,['coronavirus'],Twitter Web App,1263,3090,2020-07-12 17:37:23,False,[''],"{'neg': 0.155, 'neu': 0.845, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5106}"
187,,🍍#FeedingAmerica and its 200 member #foodbanks are still getting it done. Find out how you can support or continue to support that effort. 👇🏾#foodbank #Hawaii #hunger #coronavirus #COVID19 #pandemic ,KeshaGreen4U,,"['FeedingAmerica', 'foodbanks', 'foodbank', 'Hawaii', 'hunger', 'coronavirus', 'COVID19', 'pandemic']",Twitter Web App,226,368,2020-07-12 17:37:23,False,"[('FeedingAmerica', 'ORG'), ('200', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hawaii', 'GPE'), '', '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.833, 'pos': 0.167, 'compound': 0.6597}"
188,," 🚨BREAKING: #Florida reports a staggering 15,300 new #coronavirus cases, shattering the single-day record of any state—pr…",CaroleS54218418,"Sacramento, CA","['Florida', 'coronavirus']",Twitter for Android,634,697,2020-07-12 17:37:22,False,"[('Florida', 'GPE'), ('15,300', 'CARDINAL'), ('the single-day', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
189,, Coronavirus: Why everyone was wrong--The immune response to the virus is stronger than everyone thought,unperturbable,IMBY,[],Twitter for Android,4633,4883,2020-07-12 17:37:22,False,"[('Coronavirus', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.73, 'pos': 0.27, 'compound': 0.5859}"
190,," . is releasing 8,000 inmates due to #coronavirus fears! 🤬 I’m fed up with his “leadership.” I’m seriously cons…",rebekka416,Canada,['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPhone,2424,2061,2020-07-12 17:37:19,False,"[('8,000', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.242, 'neu': 0.758, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5848}"
191,, The Honduras #sugar industry continues to do its part in helping people during the #coronavirus pandemic. Another example th…,AzucaralDia,Honduras,"['sugar', 'coronavirus']",Twitter for iPhone,193,14,2020-07-12 17:37:16,False,"[('Honduras', 'GPE'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.891, 'pos': 0.109, 'compound': 0.296}"
192,, 148 new UK #coronavirus deaths recorded in past 24hrs.That’s the highest Saturday fatality number for a month &amp; 3x yester…,MarkHepNational,,['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPhone,50,75,2020-07-12 17:37:16,False,"[('148', 'CARDINAL'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('past 24hrs', 'DATE'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('a month &amp', 'DATE'), ('3x', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.197, 'neu': 0.746, 'pos': 0.057, 'compound': -0.6369}"
193,,We should be hearing massive Explosions all around the USA right now with Liberal heads Exploding in Unison! 😉 #wayfairchildtrafficking #AllLivesMatter #AmericaFirst #coronavirus #WWG1WGAWORLDWIDE #Entaglement #BlueLivesMatter ,tillerylakelady,Some Where USA,"['wayfairchildtrafficking', 'AllLivesMatter', 'AmericaFirst', 'coronavirus', 'WWG1WGAWORLDWIDE', 'Entaglement', 'BlueLivesMatter']",Twitter for iPhone,6714,7248,2020-07-12 17:37:15,False,"[('USA', 'GPE'), ('Liberal', 'NORP'), ('Unison', 'GPE'), ('AmericaFirst', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
194,," In #TheGreat38th- at a  dinner not even in his district, not a mask in sight, &amp; the worst week o…",coralgableswang,"Coral Gables, FL",['TheGreat38th'],Twitter for iPhone,198,515,2020-07-12 17:37:15,False,"[('TheGreat38th-', 'MONEY'), ('the worst week', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.194, 'neu': 0.806, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6249}"
195,," So it looks like the GOP's strategy to use the #coronavirus pandemic as a holocaust against POCs, old folks, disabled f…",attaboy_luther,Upstate Manhattan,['coronavirus'],Tweetbot for iΟS,312,548,2020-07-12 17:37:15,False,"[('GOP', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.873, 'pos': 0.127, 'compound': 0.4144}"
196,, Coronavirus: Why everyone was wrong--The immune response to the virus is stronger than everyone thought,obey_kenobi,,[],Twitter for Android,265,382,2020-07-12 17:37:14,False,"[('Coronavirus', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.73, 'pos': 0.27, 'compound': 0.5859}"
197,, ‼️37-year-old #Ohio veteran—who posted a widely shared anti-#mask screed on Facebook—tested positive for #COVID19 on Jul…,TRMJr,"Hayward, CA ","['Ohio', 'mask', 'COVID19']",Twitter for iPhone,112,182,2020-07-12 17:37:14,False,"[('Ohio', 'GPE'), ('Facebook', 'ORG'), ('Jul', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.684, 'pos': 0.316, 'compound': 0.7184}"
198,,"So when those infected kids go back to school in #Florida and other states after the fun time at #DisneyWorld, they can infect teachers and all the other adults in schools. Apparently, the #GOP, #Trump, and #DeSantis haven't yet met their targets for #coronavirus contagion. ",LuBonLez,"Honolulu, HI","['Florida', 'DisneyWorld', 'GOP', 'Trump', 'DeSantis', 'coronavirus']",Twitter for Android,39326,37812,2020-07-12 17:37:14,False,"[('Florida', 'GPE'), ('DisneyWorld', 'ORG'), ('GOP', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.125, 'neu': 0.811, 'pos': 0.064, 'compound': -0.4877}"
199,, Trump wearing the mask like thisEffective? 🙄🙄😂😂😂😂😂😷😷😷😷😷#Covid_19 #coronavirus ,Angusschuurman,,"['Covid_19', 'coronavirus']",Twitter for iPhone,2259,2942,2020-07-12 17:37:13,False,"[('🙄🙄', 'FAC'), ('😷', 'CARDINAL'), ('😷', 'CARDINAL'), ('😷', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.737, 'pos': 0.263, 'compound': 0.3612}"
200,, ‼️37-year-old #Ohio veteran—who posted a widely shared anti-#mask screed on Facebook—tested positive for #COVID19 on Jul…,Lisa90295545,USA,"['Ohio', 'mask', 'COVID19']",Twitter for iPad,310,486,2020-07-12 17:37:13,False,"[('Ohio', 'GPE'), ('Facebook', 'ORG'), ('Jul', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.684, 'pos': 0.316, 'compound': 0.7184}"
201,,Will #Coronavirus Kill UK Music Festivals? (White),ScottLucas_EA,"Birmingham, UK",['Coronavirus'],TweetDeck,9502,4433,2020-07-12 17:37:12,False,"[('Coronavirus Kill UK Music Festivals', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.385, 'neu': 0.41, 'pos': 0.205, 'compound': -0.4939}"
202,," . is releasing 8,000 inmates due to #coronavirus fears! 🤬 I’m fed up with his “leadership.” I’m seriously cons…",Kllyreed,"Wisconsin, USA",['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPhone,58,220,2020-07-12 17:37:12,False,"[('8,000', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.242, 'neu': 0.758, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5848}"
203,,#coronavirus #Covid_19#thoughtoftheday #fun #dontgetoffended #smileHow's the thought that once corona will get over we will refer to the year before 2020 as BC(Before Corona) and after 2020 as AC(After Corona)🤣🤣🤣,Moinudd55669357,"Mumbai, India","['coronavirus', 'Covid_19', 'thoughtoftheday', 'fun', 'dontgetoffended', 'smile']",Twitter for Android,0,16,2020-07-12 17:37:12,False,"['', '', '', '', ('the year before 2020', 'DATE'), ('BC(Before Corona', 'PERSON'), ('2020', 'DATE'), ('AC(After Corona', 'PERSON'), ('🤣🤣🤣', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
204,, 60+ US troops are infected with #coronavirus in #Okinawa.Trump does N O T care. He has turned his back on the Americ…,TheUnicorn999,"California, USA","['coronavirus', 'Okinawa']",Twitter Web App,21699,19484,2020-07-12 17:37:11,False,"[('60', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE'), '', ('Okinawa', 'GPE'), ('Americ', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.137, 'neu': 0.726, 'pos': 0.137, 'compound': 0.0}"
205,," Who is gonna tell your boy  that the Boogeyman has been found and is saying, you have 15,299 NEW #coronaviru…",Nek25P,"Detroit, MI",[],Twitter for iPhone,150,766,2020-07-12 17:37:11,False,"[('Boogeyman', 'NORP'), ('15,299', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
206,," As if you needed any more proof that Betsy DeVos is a blithering idiot, Dana Bash just smashed her face in for about 20 mins. N…",NaattuVarthakal,കേരളം,[],Naattuvartha,2868,4701,2020-07-12 17:37:10,False,"[('Betsy DeVos', 'PERSON'), ('Dana Bash', 'PERSON'), ('about 20', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.121, 'neu': 0.879, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5106}"
207,," . is releasing 8,000 inmates due to #coronavirus fears! 🤬 I’m fed up with his “leadership.” I’m seriously cons…",2020Elections2,,['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPhone,34,178,2020-07-12 17:37:10,False,"[('8,000', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.242, 'neu': 0.758, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5848}"
208,," 🔊 #PODCAST Pollster  joins host  to talk presidency, pandemic and a PM in a pickle. Plus pundit…",TerryBlott,,['PODCAST'],Twitter for iPhone,773,1511,2020-07-12 17:37:09,False,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
209,,Wear lab glasses or wrap around sunglasses when inside places with potentially #Covid_19 infected individuals to protect your eyes from the #coronavirus in aerosols floating around.#buildings #grocery #shopping ,MichaelsRocks,Canada/USA,"['Covid_19', 'coronavirus', 'buildings', 'grocery', 'shopping']",Twitter Web App,38,504,2020-07-12 17:37:08,False,"['', '', '', '']","{'neg': 0.101, 'neu': 0.818, 'pos': 0.082, 'compound': -0.1531}"
210,,"As if you needed any more proof that Betsy DeVos is a blithering idiot, Dana Bash just smashed her face in for about 20 mins. No plan, sticking to her ""kids need to go back to school"". No shit Sherlock -  but SAFELY!!!#coronavirus #COVID #covid19  ",brasqo,"New York, NY","['coronavirus', 'COVID', 'covid19']",Twitter Web App,2679,805,2020-07-12 17:37:08,False,"[('Betsy DeVos', 'PERSON'), ('Dana Bash', 'PERSON'), ('about 20', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.179, 'neu': 0.821, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.7598}"
211,, Air India announces 14 more flights between India and UK under Vande Bharat Mission | via  #AirIndia #VandeBh…,prameshjain12,proud Indian ,['AirIndia'],Twitter for Android,3012,3298,2020-07-12 17:37:08,False,"[('Air India', 'ORG'), ('14', 'CARDINAL'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Vande Bharat Mission |', 'LAW'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
212,,Yes! I see this all over in my community 🤦‍♂️😷#WearADamnMask #COVID #coronavirus ,dleighlaw,Greater New York City,"['WearADamnMask', 'COVID', 'coronavirus']",Twitter for iPhone,17,181,2020-07-12 17:37:08,False,"[('😷', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.77, 'pos': 0.23, 'compound': 0.4574}"
213,," If you took today's SINGLE day confirmed Coronavirus cases in FL, they easily beat the WEEKLY confirmed cases for entire…",RussWKYC,"Cleveland, Ohio",[],Twitter for iPhone,16246,8790,2020-07-12 17:37:06,True,"[('today', 'DATE'), ('SINGLE day', 'DATE'), ('Coronavirus', 'PERSON'), ('FL', 'GPE'), ('WEEKLY', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.888, 'pos': 0.112, 'compound': 0.34}"
214,,Pachter Factor S5E42 with  is on our YouTube channel for all! Will any good come from the coronavirus?#COVID19 #coronavirus ,SIFTDgames,"Los Angeles, CA","['COVID19', 'coronavirus']",TweetDeck,2094,364,2020-07-12 17:37:06,False,"[('YouTube', 'PRODUCT')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.849, 'pos': 0.151, 'compound': 0.4926}"
215,," #UPDATE ""The people must stay at home,"" said health official Alba Verges from Spain's Catalonia regional government, as cases of t…",StefMylesTennis,StephMylesTennis@hotmail.com,['UPDATE'],TweetDeck,3817,1790,2020-07-12 17:37:05,False,"['', ('UPDATE', 'ORG'), ('Alba Verges', 'ORG'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Catalonia', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
216,, ‼️37-year-old #Ohio veteran—who posted a widely shared anti-#mask screed on Facebook—tested positive for #COVID19 on Jul…,questella,"Ohio, USA","['Ohio', 'mask', 'COVID19']",Twitter for Android,720,641,2020-07-12 17:37:05,False,"[('Ohio', 'GPE'), ('Facebook', 'ORG'), ('Jul', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.684, 'pos': 0.316, 'compound': 0.7184}"
217,," ⚠️As students have returned to campus, officials have been warning about an alarming spike in #COVID19 cases related to…",JanSchachern,,['COVID19'],Twitter for iPhone,170,381,2020-07-12 17:37:05,False,"[('️As', 'CARDINAL'), ('COVID19', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.187, 'neu': 0.813, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4404}"
218,," In #TheGreat38th- at a  dinner not even in his district, not a mask in sight, &amp; the worst week o…",KristiCornettTN,Tennessee District 18,['TheGreat38th'],Twitter for iPhone,16940,17341,2020-07-12 17:37:04,True,"[('TheGreat38th-', 'MONEY'), ('the worst week', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.194, 'neu': 0.806, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6249}"
219,, Democrats reviewing their platform #Trump2020LandslideVictory #KAG2020 #Tcot #Ccot#COVID19 #coronavirus #WalkAway #Saturday…,BryonnyM,,"['Trump2020LandslideVictory', 'KAG2020', 'Tcot', 'Ccot', 'COVID19', 'coronavirus', 'WalkAway']",Twitter for iPad,27706,15079,2020-07-12 17:37:04,False,"[('Democrats', 'NORP'), ('Ccot#COVID19', 'ORG'), '', ('Saturday', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
220,, For the latest in Coronavirus testing and what to do if you think you may have symptoms visit: ,RigbyHsch,"Bromsgrove, England",[],Twitter for iPhone,428,299,2020-07-12 17:37:03,False,"[('Coronavirus', 'NORP')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
221,,We are closed today.  Please also note our early close hours of service.  We're taking all the precautions we can to bring you fresh food while keeping our workers safe. #coronavirus #socialdistancing ,chicksnsalsa,"Glen Ellyn, IL","['coronavirus', 'socialdistancing']",Twitter for iPhone,310,258,2020-07-12 17:37:03,False,"[('today', 'DATE'), ('our early close hours', 'TIME'), '', '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.795, 'pos': 0.205, 'compound': 0.7579}"
222,, #Devos could care less abt children And what about educators &amp; adult support staff? The average age of teachers is 50 Prime targets&gt;#Coronavirus We really don't have data abt children I can tell you as a former elementary &amp; high school teacher Youth difficult to #SocialDistance,paz4u,California Dreamin',"['Devos', 'Coronavirus', 'SocialDistance']",Twitter for Android,4561,4339,2020-07-12 17:37:03,False,"[('Devos', 'PERSON'), ('50', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.051, 'neu': 0.83, 'pos': 0.119, 'compound': 0.5267}"
223,, #Homeopathy ( ) has never claimed #Arsalb30 as curative for Corona... It was introduced as an IMMUNE BOOSTER!…,sinceresyam0000,"Tuni, India","['Homeopathy', 'Arsalb30']",Twitter for Android,11,8,2020-07-12 17:37:02,False,"[('Homeopathy', 'PERSON'), ('Arsalb30', 'MONEY'), ('Corona', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.823, 'pos': 0.177, 'compound': 0.4981}"
224,, Nna i was never afraid of getting tested like for #HIV but as for #CoronaVirus ijo so please help me God 🙏🏿🏃🏾‍♂️🏃🏾‍♂️🏃🏾‍♂️,2ddi_SA,Sedawa,"['HIV', 'CoronaVirus']",Twitter Web App,146,452,2020-07-12 17:37:02,False,"['', ('CoronaVirus ijo', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.579, 'pos': 0.421, 'compound': 0.9073}"
225,, Wow. So this is a thing. We are a #coronavirus super spreader. Japan has to tell us to FIX YOUR SH!T. We suck ev…,TheUnicorn999,"California, USA",['coronavirus'],Twitter Web App,21699,19484,2020-07-12 17:37:02,False,"[('Japan', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.097, 'neu': 0.636, 'pos': 0.267, 'compound': 0.7263}"
226,,Remember #Florida is the only place you have to go Up to go South. #coronavirus #,frism,"New York, NY","['Florida', 'coronavirus']",Twitter for iPhone,462,1029,2020-07-12 17:37:02,False,"[('Florida', 'GPE'), ('South', 'LOC'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
227,, Coronavirus: Why everyone was wrong--The immune response to the virus is stronger than everyone thought,JoshuaPMason1,,[],Twitter for iPhone,139,45,2020-07-12 17:37:02,False,"[('Coronavirus', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.73, 'pos': 0.27, 'compound': 0.5859}"
228,,17 new cases in Sierra Leone [18:37 GMT] #coronavirus #CoronaVirusUpdate #COVID19 #CoronavirusPandemic,COVIDLive,,"['coronavirus', 'CoronaVirusUpdate', 'COVID19', 'CoronavirusPandemic']",COVID19-Updates,402,1,2020-07-12 17:37:02,False,"[('17', 'CARDINAL'), ('Sierra Leone', 'ORG'), ('18:37', 'CARDINAL'), '', '', '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
229,, I think a period of reflection on this tweet might be in order given the current circumstances around #coronavirus and th…,jackalsbynight,London,['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPhone,3733,4940,2020-07-12 17:37:02,False,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
230,," . is releasing 8,000 inmates due to #coronavirus fears! 🤬 I’m fed up with his “leadership.” I’m seriously cons…",jack_ktk,"British Columbia, Canada",['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPhone,40,142,2020-07-12 17:37:01,False,"[('8,000', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.242, 'neu': 0.758, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5848}"
231,," . is releasing 8,000 inmates due to #coronavirus fears! 🤬 I’m fed up with his “leadership.” I’m seriously cons…",justalazyuser,,['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPhone,7,92,2020-07-12 17:37:01,False,"[('8,000', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.242, 'neu': 0.758, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5848}"
232,, Way to go OhioIt’s a thing of beauty 👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸#Trump2020 #KAG2020 #SaturdayThoughts #Ccot#CNNSOTU #MediaBu…,ShirleyRinguet5,"Florida, USA","['Trump2020', 'KAG2020', 'SaturdayThoughts', 'Ccot', 'CNNSOTU']",Twitter for iPhone,13139,2669,2020-07-12 17:37:00,False,"[('OhioIt', 'CARDINAL'), ('🏻', 'PRODUCT'), ('🏻', 'PRODUCT'), ('🏻', 'PRODUCT'), ('🏻', 'MONEY'), ('🇸', 'ORG'), ('🇸', 'GPE'), ('🇸', 'GPE'), ('🇸', 'GPE'), ('🇸', 'GPE'), ('🇸', 'GPE'), ('🇸', 'GPE'), ('🇸', 'GPE'), '', ('SaturdayThoughts', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.743, 'pos': 0.257, 'compound': 0.5859}"
233,, Way to go OhioIt’s a thing of beauty 👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸#Trump2020 #KAG2020 #SaturdayThoughts #Ccot#CNNSOTU #MediaBu…,fordmotorco84,"Pittsfield, MI","['Trump2020', 'KAG2020', 'SaturdayThoughts', 'Ccot', 'CNNSOTU']",Twitter for iPhone,768,1058,2020-07-12 17:36:59,False,"[('OhioIt', 'CARDINAL'), ('🏻', 'PRODUCT'), ('🏻', 'PRODUCT'), ('🏻', 'PRODUCT'), ('🏻', 'MONEY'), ('🇸', 'ORG'), ('🇸', 'GPE'), ('🇸', 'GPE'), ('🇸', 'GPE'), ('🇸', 'GPE'), ('🇸', 'GPE'), ('🇸', 'GPE'), ('🇸', 'GPE'), '', ('SaturdayThoughts', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.743, 'pos': 0.257, 'compound': 0.5859}"
234,," ⚠️Health officials in #Australia warn that child-to-child transmission of #coronavirus is ""more apparent"" than first tho…",iamabutterfly34,"Victoria, Australia ","['Australia', 'coronavirus']",Twitter for Android,17,385,2020-07-12 17:36:59,False,"[('Australia', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.085, 'neu': 0.915, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.1027}"
235,, oh hai! I'm here with a friendly reminder that  has no plans to regularly test any of their employees #disneyworl…,weissman247,"Sacramento, CA",[],Twitter for Android,339,707,2020-07-12 17:36:59,False,[''],"{'neg': 0.097, 'neu': 0.749, 'pos': 0.154, 'compound': 0.3164}"
236,, Wake Up Disney and fans! #NoSocialDistancing #Florida #coronavirus ,DeepShAIte,,"['NoSocialDistancing', 'Florida', 'coronavirus']",Twitter for iPad,77,296,2020-07-12 17:36:58,False,"['', ('Florida', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
237,," 24% of the #coronavirus deaths in #Bangladesh are taking place at home. Between 1 July and 8 July, 349 people died. Amo…",PrantickMehrab,"Dhaka, Bangladesh","['coronavirus', 'Bangladesh']",Twitter for Android,38,176,2020-07-12 17:36:56,False,"[('24%', 'PERCENT'), '', '', ('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('Between 1 July and 8 July', 'DATE'), ('349', 'CARDINAL'), ('Amo', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.159, 'neu': 0.841, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5574}"
238,, I used a magnetic pulse device to destroy the Hepatitis B virus from my liver - as the liver acts as a reservoir to the Hep B…,inabster,"London, UK",[],Twitter Web App,32554,31077,2020-07-12 17:36:56,False,"[('Hep', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.143, 'neu': 0.857, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5423}"
239,, ‼️37-year-old #Ohio veteran—who posted a widely shared anti-#mask screed on Facebook—tested positive for #COVID19 on Jul…,theReal_Rebel,,"['Ohio', 'mask', 'COVID19']",Twitter for iPhone,2733,1378,2020-07-12 17:36:55,False,"[('Ohio', 'GPE'), ('Facebook', 'ORG'), ('Jul', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.684, 'pos': 0.316, 'compound': 0.7184}"
240,, #Coronavirus report: India reports record spike as cases double in South Africa ~ #CoronavirusPandemic,adymunava,Harare,"['Coronavirus', 'CoronavirusPandemic']",Twitter for iPhone,355,608,2020-07-12 17:36:54,False,"['', ('Coronavirus', 'NORP'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('South Africa', 'GPE'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
241,," The only politicians NOT reporting to work are the DEMOCRATS who have NO morals and are just staying home to (1) keep the #coronavirus lie going, (2) campaign themelves, and (3) vacation &amp; party!#DemocratsAreVileDishonestLiberalHacks",MomsLuvTrump,"Pacific Northwest, USA","['coronavirus', 'DemocratsAreVileDishonestLiberalHacks']",Twitter Web App,10391,9718,2020-07-12 17:36:52,False,"[('DEMOCRATS', 'NORP'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('3', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.089, 'neu': 0.911, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4981}"
242,," From which 'Jamaat', Anupam Kher's mother and brother got #Coronavirus?",prameshjain12,proud Indian ,['Coronavirus'],Twitter for Android,3012,3298,2020-07-12 17:36:52,False,"[(""Anupam Kher's"", 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
243,," Philadelphia is evicting protest encampments w/ 100s of homeless people amid #coronavirus pandemic.""They can try to shut…",AtomicDoorknob,,['coronavirus'],Twitter for Android,18,197,2020-07-12 17:36:51,False,"[('Philadelphia', 'GPE'), ('100s', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.111, 'neu': 0.889, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.25}"
244,," Can using this magneto pulse device, Medicur Pro, work to get rid of #coronavirus in the lungs? - at highest 20 Hz setting sa…",inabster,"London, UK",['coronavirus'],Twitter Web App,32554,31077,2020-07-12 17:36:51,False,"[('Medicur Pro', 'PERSON'), '', ('20', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hz', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
245,,Donald trump Union League Of Philadelphia FULL Speech 9/7/16 ,FOREXEAASSARV10,"California, USA","['news', 'covid19', 'coronavirus', 'BreakingNews', 'pandemic', 'BlackPrivelage', 'WhitePrivilege', 'plandemic', 'fakepandemic', 'covidhoax', 'coronavirushoax', 'BlackLivesMatter', 'WhiteLivesMatter', 'AllLivesMatter', 'trump']",dowjonesstockmarket,2573,776,2020-07-12 17:36:51,False,"[('Union League Of Philadelphia', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
246,," If this is real, settle in w a #COVIDIOT being our leader. Gonna be a long summer. #coronavirus",Oldlady12345,"Fitchburg, WI","['COVIDIOT', 'coronavirus']",Twitter for iPhone,5552,343,2020-07-12 17:36:51,False,"[('a long summer', 'DATE'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
247,," If you took today's SINGLE day confirmed Coronavirus cases in FL, they easily beat the WEEKLY confirmed cases for entire…",OGCLEVELAND,,[],Twitter for iPhone,286,1168,2020-07-12 17:36:49,False,"[('today', 'DATE'), ('SINGLE day', 'DATE'), ('Coronavirus', 'PERSON'), ('FL', 'GPE'), ('WEEKLY', 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.888, 'pos': 0.112, 'compound': 0.34}"
248,, Disney World’s grand re-opening announcement video seems WAY more appropriate with the theme from the Shining. #Covid19 #Co…,keri_lowe_,SF,['Covid19'],Twitter for iPhone,3024,2490,2020-07-12 17:36:49,False,"[('Disney World', 'ORG'), ('WAY', 'ORG'), ('Shining', 'PRODUCT'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.85, 'pos': 0.15, 'compound': 0.4588}"
249,," ⚠️Health officials in #Australia warn that child-to-child transmission of #coronavirus is ""more apparent"" than first tho…",JanSchachern,,"['Australia', 'coronavirus']",Twitter for iPhone,170,381,2020-07-12 17:36:49,False,"[('Australia', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.085, 'neu': 0.915, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.1027}"
250,," . is releasing 8,000 inmates due to #coronavirus fears! 🤬 I’m fed up with his “leadership.” I’m seriously cons…",Big_Clell,,['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPhone,740,562,2020-07-12 17:36:46,False,"[('8,000', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.242, 'neu': 0.758, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5848}"
251,," From which 'Jamaat', Anupam Kher's mother and brother got #Coronavirus?",ajumis,Mumbai,['Coronavirus'],Twitter for Android,531,1408,2020-07-12 17:36:46,False,"[(""Anupam Kher's"", 'PERSON')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
252,, I think a period of reflection on this tweet might be in order given the current circumstances around #coronavirus and th…,MNS1947,"Buckingham, UK",['coronavirus'],Twitter Web App,358,100,2020-07-12 17:36:45,False,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
253,,I like this graph and wanted to share it. #Trump2020 #TrumpMask #TrumpVirus #MAGA #COVID #coronavirus #COVIDー19 #sundayvibes ,WintersVladimir,United States,"['Trump2020', 'TrumpMask', 'TrumpVirus', 'MAGA', 'COVID', 'coronavirus', 'COVIDー19', 'sundayvibes']",Twitter for Android,45,297,2020-07-12 17:36:41,False,"[('TrumpMask', 'GPE'), '', '', '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.749, 'pos': 0.251, 'compound': 0.5719}"
255,," John, England has a worse record than Spain on #coronavirus Can you admit that 1 point?",CraigWilliamWil,"Scotland, United Kingdom",['coronavirus'],Twitter for Android,899,946,2020-07-12 17:36:41,False,"[('John', 'PERSON'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), '', ('1', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.183, 'neu': 0.71, 'pos': 0.107, 'compound': -0.3182}"
256,, 🔴 Watch: #Coronavirus is leading many people to consider making #aliyah. Here's how to find the perfect home in Israel.…,nwarikoo,"Detroit, Michigan","['Coronavirus', 'aliyah']",Twitter for iPhone,18254,6130,2020-07-12 17:36:39,True,"['', ('Coronavirus', 'PRODUCT'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.829, 'pos': 0.171, 'compound': 0.5719}"
257,," . is releasing 8,000 inmates due to #coronavirus fears! 🤬 I’m fed up with his “leadership.” I’m seriously cons…",OregonsWarrior,"Portland, OR",['coronavirus'],Twitter for Android,576,534,2020-07-12 17:36:38,False,"[('8,000', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.242, 'neu': 0.758, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5848}"
258,, NCRI Women’s Committee calls on UN High Commissioner for Human Rights &amp; UN Special Rapporteur on the situation of human righ…,Mohamma28307078,,[],Twitter for iPhone,103,34,2020-07-12 17:36:38,False,"[('NCRI Women’s Committee', 'ORG'), ('UN', 'ORG'), ('Human Rights &amp', 'ORG'), ('UN', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.881, 'pos': 0.119, 'compound': 0.4019}"
259,," . is releasing 8,000 inmates due to #coronavirus fears! 🤬 I’m fed up with his “leadership.” I’m seriously cons…",willlholcomb,,['coronavirus'],Twitter for Android,115,677,2020-07-12 17:36:38,False,"[('8,000', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.242, 'neu': 0.758, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5848}"
260,," BREAKING: Florida smashes record for daily new #coronavirus cases with the FL Dept of Health reporting 15,300 new cases tod…",ViveYDejaVivirJ,,['coronavirus'],Twitter for iPhone,13,174,2020-07-12 17:36:36,False,"[('BREAKING', 'PERSON'), ('Florida', 'GPE'), ('daily', 'DATE'), '', ('the FL Dept of Health', 'ORG'), ('15,300', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
261,," FTA: ""That wasn’t science, but pure speculation based on a gut feeling that was then parroted by everyone."" /5 #ImmunityDeniers #coronavirus #Covid_19",1stbornAmerican,"GA, USA","['ImmunityDeniers', 'coronavirus', 'Covid_19']",Twitter for Android,5200,5083,2020-07-12 17:36:36,False,"['', ('ImmunityDeniers', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.92, 'pos': 0.08, 'compound': 0.1901}"
262,,What does is say that  probably would have done a better job #coronavirus #testing than  administration. #COVID #VoteBlue #countryoverparty,weburris,,"['coronavirus', 'testing', 'COVID', 'VoteBlue', 'countryoverparty']",Twitter for iPhone,158,397,2020-07-12 17:36:36,False,[''],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.854, 'pos': 0.146, 'compound': 0.4404}"
263,," Betsy Devos can maintain social distancing on her 163 ft yacht, while she wants children to be forced to return to school, as many as 40 students per classroom #coronavirus ",cmtwx,Las Vegas NV,['coronavirus'],TweetCaster for Android,369,881,2020-07-12 17:36:35,False,"[('Betsy Devos', 'PERSON'), ('163', 'CARDINAL'), ('as many as 40', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.094, 'neu': 0.906, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4588}"
264,, #Coronavirus: Emfuleni records three deaths ,baymenh,Vaal Triangle ,['Coronavirus'],Twitter for Android,1504,31,2020-07-12 17:36:35,False,"['', ('Coronavirus', 'NORP'), ('three', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
265,,Special treat for all race car fans! ,FaceMaskHouston,"Houston, TX","['NASCAR', 'nascarfoxsport', 'sports', 'coronavirus', 'COVID']",Twitter Web App,1,9,2020-07-12 17:36:35,False,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.468, 'pos': 0.532, 'compound': 0.69}"
266,," A lesson in leadership from  on #marr just now. Thoughtful, analytical and a total focus on protecting Sc…",AllieC9,Scotland,['marr'],Twitter for Android,299,653,2020-07-12 17:36:35,False,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.852, 'pos': 0.148, 'compound': 0.3818}"
267,,Yes to this a million times over! #coronavirus #Covid_19 #COVID #conspiracytheories #ConstitutionOverCoronavirus #cognitivedissonance,bittrsweetcaro,,"['coronavirus', 'Covid_19', 'COVID', 'conspiracytheories', 'ConstitutionOverCoronavirus', 'cognitivedissonance']",Twitter Web App,57,369,2020-07-12 17:36:33,False,"[('million', 'CARDINAL'), '', '', ('COVID', 'ORG'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.786, 'pos': 0.214, 'compound': 0.4574}"
268,,Recycling charity in Moray preparing to restart collections and deliveries again ,corona_scotnews,,"['coronavirus', 'covid19']",dlvr.it,521,0,2020-07-12 17:36:33,False,"[('Moray', 'ORG')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.781, 'pos': 0.219, 'compound': 0.4215}"
269,," . is releasing 8,000 inmates due to #coronavirus fears! 🤬 I’m fed up with his “leadership.” I’m seriously cons…",AndreAlexsen,USA,['coronavirus'],Twitter Web App,3762,4975,2020-07-12 17:36:32,False,"[('8,000', 'CARDINAL'), '']","{'neg': 0.242, 'neu': 0.758, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5848}"
270,, Warning☢️⚠️#coronavirus ,CrimAtt1,South Africa,['coronavirus'],Twitter for Android,233,264,2020-07-12 17:36:32,False,[],"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
272,," Internal documents from  warned fully reopening K-12 schools &amp; universities would pose the ""highest risk"" for spread of the…",TeeBeeDee1,NEW YORK CITY,[],Twitter Web App,10490,10308,2020-07-12 17:36:32,False,"[('K-12', 'PRODUCT')]","{'neg': 0.198, 'neu': 0.802, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4939}"
273,, The Honduras #sugar industry continues to do its part in helping people during the #coronavirus pandemic. Another example th…,AzucarHonduras,Honduras,"['sugar', 'coronavirus']",Twitter for iPhone,519,186,2020-07-12 17:36:31,False,"[('Honduras', 'GPE'), '']","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.891, 'pos': 0.109, 'compound': 0.296}"
274,, #China is suspending imports of #meat and meat products from 23 companies and stepping-up inspection of imported foods…,krupenek,,"['China', 'meat']",Twitter Web App,111,3343,2020-07-12 17:36:31,False,"['', ('China', 'GPE'), ('23', 'CARDINAL')]","{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}"
275,,Tot Dead TO  ON     CDA7/12      1117 5686 18965#CdnPoli #ONpoli #TOpoli #CanLab #CdnLab #ONlab #RightToRefuse #PPE #PaidLeave #UnionWorker #Test #LTC #CoronaVirus #SARSVirus #Medicare #PayEquity #ExcessDeaths #UBI #CERB #ChildCare  #Pandemic #USBorder #Airports ,IamTomBaker,"Burlington, ON.","['CdnPoli', 'ONpoli', 'TOpoli', 'CanLab', 'CdnLab', 'ONlab', 'RightToRefuse', 'PPE', 'PaidLeave', 'UnionWorker', 'Test', 'LTC', 'CoronaVirus', 'SARSVirus', 'Medicare', 'PayEquity', 'ExcessDeaths', 'UBI', 'CERB', 'ChildCare', 'Pandemic', 'USBorder', 'Airports']",Twitter Web App,479,252,2020-07-12 17:36:31,False,"[('Tot Dead', 'PERSON'), ('CDA7/12      ', 'ORG'), '', '', '', ('UnionWorker', 'ORG'), '', '', ('CoronaVirus', 'ORG'), ('Medicare', 'ORG'), '', '', '', ('ChildCare', 'ORG'), '', '']","{'neg': 0.129, 'neu': 0.871, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6486}"
276,," In #TheGreat38th- at a  dinner not even in his district, not a mask in sight, &amp; the worst week o…",StyrStyx,💘MrPiddles! #Fresh 🔄 #Hanian,['TheGreat38th'],Twitter Web App,4608,4619,2020-07-12 17:36:30,False,"[('TheGreat38th-', 'MONEY'), ('the worst week', 'DATE')]","{'neg': 0.194, 'neu': 0.806, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6249}"
